<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Latest CareerBuilder Jobs: New York, NY, US - 30 mile radius</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobresults.aspx?strcrit=st%3da%3buse%3dANY%3bTID%3d0%3bCTY%3dNew+York%3bSID%3dNY%3bCID%3dUS%3bLOCCID%3dUS%3bENR%3dNO%3bDTP%3dDRNS%3bYDI%3dYES%3bIND%3dALL%3bPDQ%3dAll%3bPDQ%3dAll%3bPAYL%3d0%3bPAYH%3dgt120%3bPOY%3dNO%3bETD%3dALL%3bRE%3dALL%3bMGT%3dDC%3bSUP%3dDC%3bFRE%3d30%3bQS%3dADVSEARCHFRM%3bSS%3dNO%3bTITL%3d0%3bOB%3d-relv%3bRAD%3d30%3bJQT%3dRAD%3bJDV%3dFalse%3bHost%3dUS%3bSITEENT%3dUSJob%3bMaxLowExp%3d-1%3bRecsPerPage%3d500</link><description>Latest CareerBuilder Jobs</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 20:30:10 Z</pubDate><item><title>Restaurant Manager - Wendy's</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP44N60GZLRWQVJM57&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP44N60GZLRWQVJM57&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Restaurant Management Positions with Wendy's / The Briad Group WE ARE GROWING !! If you're a born leader, then you've stumbled across the right job for you. Wendy's fast food restaurant is looking for a motivated restaurant manager to join their fast-paced, energetic team! The perfect restaurant manager will be a confident decision-maker who has experience in guest and customer service, employee management, business and financial management, and people motivation. S/he will be an excellent communicator – both in written form and verbally. The next Wendy's Restaurant Manager will: Execute service at the highest level Work with the leadership team to meet sales goals Manage operational costs Manage a team of talented employees eager to engage Interview and hire team members Provide proper training and coaching of team members Maintain fast, accurate service, provide excellent customer service, and exceed both company and customer expectations Ensure the continual improvement of Quality, Service and Cleanliness Our Restaurant Managers help to support the company and the communities we serve by maintaining an outstanding work environment by providing leadership, direction, training, and development of assistant managers and team members alike. REQUIREMENTS Two years prior restaurant experience minimum College degree or equivalent experience in operations Management/Supervisory/Mentor experience required Guest-friendly demeanor COMPANY BENEFITS 401k Medical Dental Bonus Opportunity Vacations Sick Time About The Briad Group® The Briad Group is headquartered in Livingston, N.J. , and is one of the fastest growing hospitality companies in the U.S. The Briad Group’s entities are: licensed franchisees for Wendy's, T.G.I. Friday's®, Corner Bakery Cafe, Marriott, Hilton and a licensee for Zinburger Wine &amp; Burger Bar. The Briad Group also owns and operates CUPS Frozen Yogurt - That's Hot ™ , a self-serve frozen yogurt concept that is poised for explosive growth. Ready to lead with us? Apply for the Wendy's Restaurant Manager position now. Click “Apply Now" to get started . Briad Restaurant Management, LLC is an EOE. We are an eVerify employer. Apply today and be a part of this growing brand!</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Audit Senior</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J5LL71GT018WZ909V&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J5LL71GT018WZ909V&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: RESPONSIBILITIES: Kforce has a client seeking a highly motivated Audit Senior for their New York, NY office. This is an opportunity to grow and advance in a leadership role at a growing firm, supervise and coach staff on diverse engagements, and deliver outstanding service to your clients. The primary responsibilities of this position include: Execute and assist in planning multiple audit engagements Supervise and coach staff on engagements and deliver outstanding service to your clients Partner with clients and firm management through timely and effective communication Develop relationships with clients Learn and understand your client's business Manage and complete the engagements on a daily basis through detailed planning, budgeting, proactive problem solving, and staff management Train and coach audit staff Effectively delegate to and challenge staff Handle directly more complex aspects of the audit as needed Review and evaluate work prepared by Staff before submission to the Manager, Managing Director and Quality Control Share constructive feedback regarding the performance of staff</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Executive Chef</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM6336XLL53BVF1ZBJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM6336XLL53BVF1ZBJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job Description: This is an exciting opportunity for an energetic, entrepreneurial Culinary professional who is constantly seeking a better way to conduct business. This key leadership position is directly responsible for the successful operation of the Culinary Department in an Acute Care Hospital. The Executive Chef ensures client, customer service/satisfaction with efficient cost effective management meeting and exceeding stated expectations. You will be responsible for all foodservice related activities which includes managing the daily operations of the kitchen area, implementing the production process, managing food cost / labor cost and having overall understanding of HACCP, under the direction of the Director of Food and Nutrition. You will also be responsible for developing, mentoring and coaching internal associates. If you are a Culinary Professional seeking a position with a fantastic quality of life environment and growth opportunities, then you do not want to miss out on this great opportunity. Join our team and be eligible for comprehensive medical and dental benefits, relocation assistance, a matching 401K plan, and many other benefits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid Level Developer .Net C#</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H0GH6C1H32H4JSDQ2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H0GH6C1H32H4JSDQ2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: RESPONSIBILITIES: Kforce is seeking a .Net Developer to join the development team with a premier client in Tempe, AZ. They are looking for a candidate who has experience with Web Applications and Content Management. The qualified candidate will be comfortable in a collaboration environment, working alongside the rest of the team to deliver a great product. It is a -no-ego- environment where everyone works together in an agile and equal culture.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr. Project Manager</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F2D966055DB5QR0Y6&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F2D966055DB5QR0Y6&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Sr. Project Manager Denver, CO Duration: 06/30/2014 This position requires a senior level project manager due to the fact that it crosses agency boundaries, and covers a variety of early childhood programs, some of which are not managed by the state. The complicated nature of the project organization and statutes driving this work requires a project manager with complex organizational skills, and one that can manage many concurrent activities at one time and keep the team focused on the goal. Engagement begins as soon as candidate is hired, and ends on June 30, 2014 (there may be an option to extend for 6 months). Hours per week are flexible; but will average between 32 and 40 hours per week. Type Qualification Description Competency Experience Skills Agile Advanced 6-7 yrs Skills Bachelor's Degree Expert 4-5 yrs Skills Business Analyst Proficient 3-4 yrs Skills Data Analysis Proficient 2-3 yrs Skills PMP Expert 10+ yrs Skills Project management Expert 10+ yrs Skills SDLC Advanced 5-6 yrs</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Account Executive</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM64H6VQVD1Q1VFDBG&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM64H6VQVD1Q1VFDBG&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Position Summary: As a Screenvision Account Executive based in the Houston, TX region, you will be a consultative advertising advisor to the area’s most successful local businesses. Working within this defined sales territory you’ll identify the unique needs of prospective customers and develop cinema advertising solutions which meet those needs. Strong communication and selling skills combined with a can-do attitude will ensure your success. Outside media sales background and experience in working with local businesses is required. Upon joining the team, we will provide comprehensive training for all aspects of Cinema ad sales to ensure a successful market entry. Screenvision offers a fun, fast-paced environment that recognizes and rewards its employees with a variety of benefits: Base salary Generous commission plan Car allowance Expense reimbursement Performance recognition program Medical, dental and vision insurance Paid vacation 401(k) plan</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>AUTOMOTIVE DIESEL TECHNICIAN / AUTOMOTIVE MECHANIC / FORD AUTO TECH</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV3RQ73Y85L69J40LN&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV3RQ73Y85L69J40LN&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Ford Automotive DIESEL Technicians / Automotive DIESEL Mechanics Isn’t it time you took your automotive diesel service technician / auto tech career further? Job Description Automotive Diesel Technicians perform work specified on maintenance and repair orders on Diesel Vehicles with efficiency and in accordance with dealership and/or Ford standards Diesel automotive technicians diagnose and repair vehicle automotive systems including engine, transmission, electrical, steering, suspension, braking, air conditioning, etc. to specification Diesel Mechanics provide labor and time estimates for additional automotive repairs Explain diesel mechanical diagnoses and required repairs in a non-technical manner to service advisors and customers Continuously learn new technical information and techniques in formal training sessions in order to stay abreast with rapidly changing technology. Inspect and test new vehicles and recording findings so that necessary repairs can be made. AUTOMOTIVE DIESEL TECHNICIAN / AUTOMOTIVE MECHANIC / FORD AUTO TECH</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Staff Analyst, Planning &amp; Hedge Administration</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H4F76WFL14DB0CBZB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H4F76WFL14DB0CBZB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Staff Analyst, Planning &amp; Hedge Administration- Dallas, TX - Direct HireFrontline Source Group - temporary staffing and direct hire firm - is offering an excellent opportunity to join the team of one of our top Dallas clients. Primary Function:The Staff Analyst, Planning &amp; Hedge Admin coordinates budgeting activities including capital budget oversight and collaboration with Operations; provides monthly variance commentary contained in corporate reports; compiles and presents the rolling 13 week cash flow forecast to ensure adequate liquidity; responsible for commodity price research and hedging advice; executes approved derivative contracts, administers contracts from execution to settlement, including mark to mark accounting. Positions Description:Supports budget compilation; prepares data templates and assumptions for Operations, etc.Loads approved budget into COGNOS or other softwareAssists with variance commentary regarding management or shareholder reportingPrepares ongoing cash flow forecast and financing needsCapital budget stewardship and governanceAssists with quarterly forecast updatesCommodity price research and hedging adviceExecute approved derivative contracts, maintain all required documentation to satisfy audit and SOX needsAdminister derivatives from order to interim mark to market valuation to settlementProvide accounting entry information to General AccountingPerforms other related duties and/or special projects as required Position Requirements:Bachelor’s degree in accounting or finance required.MBA and experience with commodity hedging is preferred.4-10 years of relevant experience, with most of that in financial reporting, planning, derivative trading or operations support. 2+ years oil and gas experience via industry or audit.ERP and reporting tools; COGNOS a plus. In order to speed up the interview process, we invite you to create a video profile for immediate review: http://bit.ly/1hXcnYZ. This tool is cutting the number of interviews it takes to get to the offer, so we welcome you to take advantage of this wonderful tool. Please visit us on the web at http://www.frontlinesourcegroup.com/dallas.htm Equal Opportunity Employer, M/F/V/D. Candidates must have authorization to work in the U.S. Clients will not sponsor visas. Frontline Source Group™ is one of the fastest growing Information Technology, Accounting, Legal, Human Resources, Administrative, and Clerical staffing and direct hire firms with offices throughout Texas (Arlington, Austin, Dallas, Fort Worth, Plano, Houston Galleria, Lewisville, West Houston, San Antonio, Sugar Land, and The Woodlands), Tennessee (Nashville and Brentwood), Arizona (Phoenix and Scottsdale), and Oklahoma (Oklahoma City). Denver, Colorado coming soon Frontline specializes in matching top talent with companies for direct, contract, and contract-to-hire placements. We work with clients and candidates in all areas of the United States.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Receptionist</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J63N62QKNVSY7L7TJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J63N62QKNVSY7L7TJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: We are looking for a professional Telephone Operator/Receptionist to represent our company. Requirements: Will answer phones and transfer accordingly. Will work on assignments that are routine in nature where limited judgment is required. Normally receives detailed instructions on all work. Will do computer work per instructions by manager.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Child Care Center Assistant Director</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J5ZZ6661QGBLH67L8&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J5ZZ6661QGBLH67L8&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Our organization prides itself on excellence, putting the education and development of our children first and foremost. When you consider a career at Learning Care Group, know you will be joining a team that is passionate about thoroughly preparing their students for all the challenges that lie ahead. As an Assistant Director, parents, teachers, and your Director will look to you for answers, direction and assistance. You will be trusted with a wide range of tasks that will be essential to the smooth running of the School as well as to the educational development of the children. Some of the exciting things that you will do as an Assistant Director include, but are not limited to: Make a difference every day! Assist the Director with the operation of the school, ensuring that the school is operating in accordance with company and state licensing standards. Be responsible for ensuring an educational, caring and safe environment for the children and parents. Spark imagination, build self-esteem and help children discover new things each day. Teach, educate and monitor children as needed. Assist Director in staff development and training. Promote the positive image of the company and play a major role in making the company a provider of choice in educational programs for the communities that we service. Help achieve profitability for the company.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Assistant Store Managers Needed!</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB7178689LRTVY52Z27&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB7178689LRTVY52Z27&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: This position assists the Store Manager with daily store activities and oversees the store operation in the absence of the Store Manager. The Lead Assistant Store Manager provides top quality service and assistance to customers; coaches store employees and works with the Store Manager to maintain a safe, cost-effective and profitable store. May cover weekend and other shifts for the Store Manager as assigned. The position includes, but is not limited to, the following essential job duties, responsibilities and requirements: JOB DUTIES &amp; RESPONSIBILITIES: Provides excellent customer service and coaches store employees to provide excellent customer service in a courteous, friendly and attentive manner to ensure the customer has a pleasant shopping experience. Covers weekend and other shifts for the Store Manager as assigned, locks and unlocks the store if necessary in mornings or at evening closings. May respond to vendor or charitable solicitations or refer to Store Manager if appropriate. Supervises and directs the activities of store employees to ensure that store product areas (including gasoline, merchandise and food service) are stocked, rotated and displayed to ensure freshness, appeal and easy customer access. Monitors overall store and property conditions; may notify Maintenance of equipment failure or maintenance/supply needs; performs or directs store employees to perform a variety of general housekeeping and routine equipment maintenance duties. Maximizes sales and profitability by supporting sales promotions and product category initiatives and by controlling labor and material expenses. Monitors and ensures that associates comply with company policies and procedures and government regulations for sales transactions and verification of eligibility to purchased age-restricted products. Assists the Store Manager in hiring, training and developing employees. Assists with scheduling employees, assigning duties to store employees and providing input to performance reviews. Keeps accurate cash, sales, food cost, payroll and inventory control records and accounts for variances. Assists with or completes banking functions, currency drops and daily deposits. Reviews and verifies employee paperwork and timekeeping records to ensure accuracy and completeness. Serves as lead “go to resource" for proprietary food planning and execution. 10. Follows vendor check-in procedures and accounts for quality and quantity of merchandise received during vendor deliveries. 11. Performs other job-related tasks as assigned.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>FileNet Admin</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL50S6ZJWJ2JM1LN1T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL50S6ZJWJ2JM1LN1T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Hi, Please review the below job details and let me know if you are interested, =============================================== Position :FileNet Administrator Location : Chelsea MA Duration : a bout 6-12 months but could be extended up to 36 months. Client is seeikng a self motivated and driven FileNet Administrator. Technical Skills and Experience Needed: 4+ years of FileNet P8 5.0 (Content engine, Process engine. Application engine) or higher experience (most recent version 5.2 preferred) 2+ years with linux (zLinux added plus) 2+ years with WAS ND 2+ years with RDBMS (DB2 added plus)</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Virtual Sr. Recruiter - Engineering/Manufacturing</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H47F6K5HCD9SQMR4W&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H47F6K5HCD9SQMR4W&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Position Description As a Senior Recruiter you are responsible for full cycle recruitment and fulfillment of your assigned requisitions. Successful candidates will be an “out of the box” thinker, process driven, and a relationship builder. They will have industry knowledge as well as expert level compliance knowledge in order to reach the best possible outcome for the candidate/client. Responsibilities include: Will recruit for high level, niche, Technical positions (Engineering/Manufacturing,Transport/Utilities) Consultative with client and candidates and has relationship building skills Ability to understand job descriptions as well as strong industry knowledge Will create job postings Screen resumes as well as job board usage Conducts and/or participates in Intake calls/requisition reviews Collaborate on sourcing plans and candidate assessment and selection Executes sourcing strategies Interview candidates Company Overview Randstad Sourceright is one of the leading providers of talent acquisition solutions in the world. Our people are the best in the business, helping us win industry recognition and client accolades year after year as innovators and top providers of Blended Workforce Solutions, RPO, MSP, and Payroll and Independent Contractor Solutions (PICS). Position Requirements Basic qualifications include: High school diploma or equivalent Minimum of 5-7 years of high level technical recruiting and sourcing experience in Engineering Manufacturing Minimum of 5-7 years of full cycle, Client Facing recruiting experience Preferred qualifications include: Ability to vet candidates for niche level technical roles Knowledge of the transport and utilities industries highly preferred Taleo experience highly preferred Strong communication skills, both verbal and written Ability to interact professionally with Candidates and Clients Proven ability to work within a team environment Ability to make decisions, take direction and execute a plan Detail orientation with follow-through shown in previous jobs Track record of proven results Expert process/system knowledge EEO Employer: Race, Religion, Color, Sex, Disability, National Origin, Age, Genetic Information, Protected Veteran Status, or any other legally protected group status.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Voted Top Places!</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM4X86307RMLJX3SRL&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM4X86307RMLJX3SRL&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Visit Our Website! Google+ Page Like Us On Facebook YouTube Channel We have been named BEST PLACE TO WORK for the second consecutive year!!! Customer Service Representative wanted for growing Marketing Firm! Full Time! Paid Training with a dedicated Corporate Trainer! Entry Level Training - Customer Service Management Development - Marketing &amp; Sales - Customer Service Mangers Campaign Sales &amp; Marketing Management - Fortune 100 Clients Customer service definition from Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia : Customer service is the provision of service to customers before, during and after a purchase. Customer service is a series of activities designed to enhance the level of customer satisfaction – that is, the feeling that a product or service has met the customer expectation. 3S Enterprises' mission is to wow our Fortune 500 clients through acquiring new customers and maintaining existing customers by providing the best customer service and services on the market and following through with our promises. Customer satisfaction is a must.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Clinical Interaction Specialist  - Temporary</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB756J6V4PN1M83261P&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB756J6V4PN1M83261P&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job is located in Naperville, IL. Exempt/Non-Exempt: Non-Exempt RSA Medical, LLC ('RSA' or the 'Company') is an outsourced provider of technology-based, medical risk management services to the individual health and life insurance industries. The Company improves the manner in which insurance companies collect applicants' medical and demographic information and make underwriting decisions. The Company believes in the advocacy of the patient in the insurance process and utilizes a Telemedicine platform to provide clinical healthcare with a real-time interactive patient and provider process. The Company's technology permits communication between patient and medical staff with both convenience and fidelity. We have chosen to specialize within the medical community by offering only experiences of exceptional quality. Our objective is to be recognized as the company that, by its deeds, shows our entire industry what sustainability is in all its dimensions: people, process, service, place, and profits. In doing so, we commit with a steadfast devotion to the needs of our clients and patients. Duties: Receives inbound calls from insurance applicants, reviews the case file and completes a medical interview to obtain the required information as designated by the TeleMed interview system. Uses a consultative approach supported by medical knowledge and defined policies and procedures to uncover and collect additional critical details (calculated, expanded questioning) regarding conditions, treatment, medication usage, recovery etc. Proactively serves as an advocate to assist the applicant in the collection of vital medical information by contacting medical care facilities and medical offices, physicians etc. to obtain information required to fully complete the medical interview. Acts as a courteous, professional medical representative and customer advocate to obtain necessary information, document collected information efficiently and credibly to ensure a complete and accurate medical interview is completed and filed with the insurance carrier. Responsible for following defined policies, procedures and standards for professional conduct, the MCM must perform within Quality standards to ensure consistent, accurate, professional client engagements. Acts in compliance with all HIPAA guidelines and standards of care in client interactions. Uses good judgment, tact and compassion to handle the delicacy of exchanging personal health information and the Adheres to a designated work schedule and consistently works schedule as expected in accordance with company attendance policy. Maintains a consistent knowledge of all Client programs which he/she has been trained on. Willingly accepts additional training toe expand skills to become capable of servicing a higher number of clients across varying client programs. Accepts responsibility for actions and executes transactions with the knowledge that every interview is confidential and information obtained requires extreme accuracy as the information collected generates legal documents which are filed with the insurance carrier. Works accurately and efficiently to maximize service to clients. Adheres to designated guidelines for phone availability and works to become highly proficient with client call transactions to assist the highest number of clients possible per day. Takes ownership of Client issues, identified system or procedural issues which are creating a negative experience for the client, are impacting their ability to perform the job efficiently or with the right level of quality. Communicates these issues through their Team leader or a Floor manager to ensure the issues are addressed. Approaches the job with a focus on quality and completing cases each day with the objective to follow policies and procedures consistently while learning and becoming more and more efficient to complete the maximum number of interviews in the shortest possible time. Works interactively with their Team Leader to discuss their own performance, obtain guidance as needed and grow their skills to continually achieve a higher level of quality and a higher Interview completion rate. Acts as an owner of the company and expects their peers to follow company policies, procedures, standards for quality and Standards for patient care. Addresses issues directly with peers who are not acting in the best interests of the Client, the Team or RSA OR informs their Team Leader of the issues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Automotive Inspector - Plainfield, NJ</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP6RV5VNJ631V626VT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP6RV5VNJ631V626VT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: SGS Automotive Services N.A. is currently seeking motivated individuals who are interested in starting a career in Automotive Inspecting. If you enjoy working in a fast-paced environment, having face to face interaction with customers and are detail oriented, this is the position for you. Our Automotive Inspectors enjoy the freedom of mobility and working with minimal supervision. We offer paid training, competitive pay, mileage reimbursement and full time benefits! JOB DESCRIPTION SGS Automotive is a vehicle inspection company for the study, development and application of technologies for motor vehicle testing, diagnostics, repair, technician training, and information management. Automotive Inspectors perform accurate and timely inspections on off lease vehicles. Inspectors act as a liaison between SGS customers and lessee’s. Specific responsibilities Drives a personal vehicle to and from inspection sites; typically lessee’s home or place of business Detects signs of damage by viewing all exterior and interior areas of the vehicle Identifies scratches, gouges, dents and dings on the vehicle Recognizes vehicle color classification Determines excessive wear and tear, chargeable and non chargeable damages Takes images of vehicles and attaches images to electronic vehicle file Enters vehicle data and damages into a hand held computer Assure the highest level of service and compliance Maintain all assigned equipment in good working order, and report malfunctions immediately</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Automotive Inspector - Culver City, CA</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHQ2SC6ND738CS8N108&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHQ2SC6ND738CS8N108&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: SGS Automotive Services N.A. is currently seeking motivated individuals who are interested in starting a career in Automotive Inspecting. If you enjoy working in a fast-paced environment, having face to face interaction with customers and are detail oriented, this is the position for you. Our Automotive Inspectors enjoy the freedom of mobility and working with minimal supervision. We offer paid training, competitive pay, mileage reimbursement and full time benefits! JOB DESCRIPTION SGS Automotive is a vehicle inspection company for the study, development and application of technologies for motor vehicle testing, diagnostics, repair, technician training, and information management. Automotive Inspectors perform accurate and timely inspections on off lease vehicles. Inspectors act as a liaison between SGS customers and lessee’s. Specific responsibilities Drives a personal vehicle to and from inspection sites; typically lessee’s home or place of business Detects signs of damage by viewing all exterior and interior areas of the vehicle Identifies scratches, gouges, dents and dings on the vehicle Recognizes vehicle color classification Determines excessive wear and tear, chargeable and non chargeable damages Takes images of vehicles and attaches images to electronic vehicle file Enters vehicle data and damages into a hand held computer Assure the highest level of service and compliance Maintain all assigned equipment in good working order, and report malfunctions immediately</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>MACY'S IS HIRING: Seasonal Retail Stock Receiving Part Time, Evening 2pm-11pm - Honolulu, HI – Ala Moana Center</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H1L86JXJ522HH6V73&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H1L86JXJ522HH6V73&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Overview: As a Seasonal Retail Stock Receiving Associate, you will be an integral part of bringing the magic of Macy's to life during the fast-paced holiday season. Associates in this role perform a number of functions that are critical to offering our customers the best experience when they shop in our store. While all seasonal positions require working as part of a team to meet department and store objectives, your individual responsibilities may include the timely execution of the receiving process, delivering merchandise to the floor for placement, ensuring floor readiness by store opening, keeping the selling floor stocked with merchandise, and organizing the selling floor and stock areas. In order to present our customers with the best holiday shopping experience, most of our Retail Stock Receiving Associates start their workday early in the morning or late in the evening to ensure we are ready to make Macy's magic. Some locations even have overnight processing schedules. Seasonal associates will have the opportunity to work a flexible schedule on a temporary basis, which may include early mornings, evenings, weekends and busy events such as the day after Thanksgiving and the day after Christmas. And don't forget - just in time for holiday shopping, you will receive an employee discount of up to 20% starting your first day! Any scheduled hours listed in the job posting title are subject to change based on business needs. All seasonal associates may be required to work hours other than those stated in the job posting title on weekends or on key holiday events, such as the Friday after Thanksgiving. Essential Functions:- Complete all processing and receiving activities in accordance with productivity standardstimelines - Responsible for customer carryout and special deliveries - Participate instockroom maintenance, organization, and housekeeping - Perform other duties as assigned - Regular, dependable attendance and punctuality Qualifications: Education/Experience: No specific education or experience required Communication Skills: Ability to read and interpret documents such as memos, safety rules, policies and procedures. Ability to communicate effectively with peers and management Mathematical Skills: Basic math functions such as addition, subtraction, multiplication, and division. Able to use a calculator Reasoning Ability: Ability to work in a fast-paced environment, handle multiple priorities, and learn new procedures. Ability to work as part of a team, but also able to complete tasks independently with little supervision Physical Demands: Position may include frequent lifting, bending, reaching, and the use of ladders and other equipment Other Skills: Demonstrates an energetic and positive attitude Work Hours: Available to work a flexible schedule, which may include early morning, evening, overnight, weekends holidays, and major sales events. Hours are subject to change based on business needs Macy's is an Equal Opportunity Employer, committed to a diverse and inclusive work environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Senior Principal Scientist (610404)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP6N0717SGKBL9RFCR&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP6N0717SGKBL9RFCR&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: COMPANY INFORMATION Leidos Biomedical Research, Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of Leidos, operates the Frederick National Laboratory for Cancer Research, sponsored by the National Cancer Institute. Our focus is on basic and applied science in cancer and AIDS. We maintain an integrated suite of advanced technologies backed by scientific expertise in areas such as genetics, genomics, protein science, proteomics, bioinformatics, high-performance biomedical computing, and nanotechnology. We develop new technologies to support cutting-edge science, and we develop and manufacture clinical-grade pharmaceuticals for first-in-human trials. For more information about Leidos Biomedical Research Inc., please visit our webpage at www.leidosbiomed.com PROGRAM DESCRIPTION The AIDS and Cancer Virus Program (ACVP), Leidos Biomedical Research, Inc., pursues multidisciplinary research programs in basic and applied molecular virology, viral immunology, and retroviral pathogenesis. JOB DESCRIPTION We are looking for a team player to play a key role in high profile, high impact scientific collaborations, with the ability to thrive in a dynamic, demanding collaborative environment that requires close attention to detail while maintaining high data quality in the face of laboratory throughput requirements and deadlines. The Senior Principal Scientist will be responsible for the operation of research support cores providing a range of critical nucleic acid based quantitative virological and sequence based viral analyses in support of high profile AIDS related studies in nonhuman primate models and clinical protocols. This position will work with the Program Director to provide overall scientific and technical direction for cores, including oversight of daily ongoing operations and staff, assessment, development, evaluation and implementation of new assays and technologies. The Senior Principal Scientist will communicate/coordinate with a variety of internal and external collaborators and be responsible for prioritization of specimen sets and analysis queue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Part Time Associate Manager</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHN4ZC72F5PSPQ6353C&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHN4ZC72F5PSPQ6353C&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Sovran Self Storage, Inc. (NYSE: SSS) is a fully integrated, self-administered and self-managed real estate investment trust (REIT) that acquires and manages self storage properties. The Company owns and/or operates more than 400 self storage facilities under the trade name Uncle Bob's Self Storage®, and serves over 160,000 customers in 25 states, making it one of the largest self-storage companies in the US. Uncle Bob’s Self Storage serves residential and commercial customers primarily with storage space rental on a month-to-month basis. Other services include moving truck rental and retail sales of boxes and moving supplies. The Company anticipates rapid growth over the next few years, and actively seeks motivated individuals with strong customer service skill and a strong attention to detail. If you would like to find out more about our company please go to www.unclebobs.com/company/ Uncle Bob's Self Storage has an immediate opening for a Part Time Associate Manager (28 hours/week) for our Katy Freeway location in Houston. Responsibilities include: Maximizing rental income Preparing leases Customer Service Handling financial transactions and banking activities Maintaining a working knowledge of all product and services Maintaining general curb appeal- sweeping and cleaning</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Electrodiagnostic Tech/Neurodiagnostic Tech</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR8FS76Y420G426FRP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR8FS76Y420G426FRP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Summary Working under the supervision of Field Operations Manager, this position is responsible for performing comprehensive Nerve Conduction Velocity (NCV) studies including Somatosensory Evoked Potential (SSEP) testing in a field setting in accordance with standard testing procedures using Cadwell Sierra Wave equipment or similar devices. Neurophysiology Technicians in this position will assist with maintaining client accounts and educating physicians on clinical diagnoses and purposes for testing. Duties And Responsibilities Responsible for performing nerve conduction velocity and somatosensory evoked potential studies using standard protocols. Provide case specific clinical notes and submitting studies to neurologist for review. Complete daily operational and administrative duties including daily upload notifications, billing charge captures, testing forecasts, and delivery of patient paperwork to the corporate office. Transport equipment to and from practices daily, often involving travel to more than one practice within a day. Follow HIPAA standards and Diversified Diagnostics LLC policy when handling and transferring confidential patient data. Communicate professionally and effectively with clients, teammates, and colleagues at all levels. Assist in account management of practices by organizing schedules, scheduling patients, and educating staff and physicians on testing modalities, procedures, and processes. Support and assist Account Manager and Field Operations Manager in building and maintaining relationships, generating new business opportunities, and the development of market growth strategies. Independently troubleshoot issues in the field when they arise and deliver prompt solutions, requesting assistance when needed. Clean and maintain all clinical equipment in compliance with ICAEL and ICAVL accreditation and Diversified Diagnostics LLC standards. Complete and maintain required certifications, registries, and continuing education.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>College Recruiter</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP0866VN5NQQF029HV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP0866VN5NQQF029HV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: College Recruiter Pioneer Pacific College is looking for candidates who recognize the value of career education and want to play a key part in helping people reach their goals. We are looking for business professionals who possess the following skills.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Aerospace Color Technician</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G09L6PF76KGT36DQC&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G09L6PF76KGT36DQC&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: AkzoNobel is a leading global paints and coatings company and a major producer of specialty chemicals, with leading market positions and brands in countries around the world. We operate in a number of important market segments ranging from buildings and infrastructure to transport, industrial and consumer goods. We’re also the sector leader in sustainability and are number one in the renowned Dow Jones Sustainability Index. In practical terms, that means our sustainable solutions are in your lives, and those of your friends and family, every day. We’re the people that make it possible for you to do what you need to do. The Color Support Technician interfaces with business critical customers (OEM, MRO, design agents, distributors) and internal customers (Sales, Marketing, Production) regarding color standards, processes, methods, and complaints. Global color alignment, accuracy, stability, and consistency of the color of our coatings is critical to customer acceptance and approval of AkzoNobel Aerospace Coatings as a supplier. The Color Support Specialist ensures that the process runs smoothly and delivers the needed results. This position is responsible for execution of color activities including: Customer Support, Complaint Investigation, Scale-up, and Color Formula Development for the Aerospace Market in North America Essential Functions 35% Technical service to external customers 35% Technical service and support to internal customers, including production and QC 30% Perform color development</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Tier 2 Software Engineer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV0GD609NTCN06B5PJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV0GD609NTCN06B5PJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Spherion is currently hiring for a fantastic direct hire opportunity as a Tier 2 Engineer with a leading firm in South Bend, IN! This opportunity offers great starting pay, full benefits, and opportunity for growth. See below and apply today! Act as Tier 2 support for our managed I.T. program Work with other support engineers on level 2 I.T. projects including server and network installation, configuration and troubleshooting; Work directly with clients to resolve issues, recommend solutions and provide I.T. consulting services Active Directory Management Remote/Terminal Services Set-up and maintenance Network wiring and troubleshooting VPN Set Up Routers and Firewalls</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>RN-Data Abstractor 1.0FTE (80hrs) Days - Franciscan System Services (0000)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F4GV5Y7RTVSJ30P4T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F4GV5Y7RTVSJ30P4T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job Summary Abstracts a large volume of clinical case records within published deadlines for continuous reporting to Catholic Health Initiatives (CHI) and The Joint Commission (TJC) in support of FHS business objectives and compliance with regulatory standards. Work involves; managing the overall record retrieval process for abstracting required data; collecting numerous complex data elements from individual patient records; ensuring the integrity of the electronic data transmitted to an established national database, keeping meticulous records and presenting results to leadership. Incumbents are also accountable for producing reports addressing variances from the regulatory standards for clinical outcomes, and identifying significant data trends, outlier values or unusual data for additional review by physicians and/or management staff. Incumbents are also accountable for maintaining current knowledge of The Joint Commission (TJC) standards, patient safety goals, and other regulatory requirements impacting matters within assigned scope of responsibility; maintaining current knowledge of data abstracting methodologies and clinical informatics through regular review of the literature, attending conferences, and participation in professional organizations, etc. Essential Duties Abstracts clinical data from multiple FHS hospitals for internal customers and external entities, in accordance with contractual requirements. Develops efficient abstracted data management processes and reporting systems. Ensures the integrity of the data by checking and auditing information submitted. Assures that abstracted data is reported to appropriate standing committees and external entities in a timely manner. Produces abstracted data using organizational software and a uniform report format to maximize organizational consistency. Enters abstracted data into web-based databases for electronic transmission to third-party vendors and subsequent transmission to CHI, The Joint Commission (TJC), and where appropriate. Develops reports and presents/explains abstracted data to various committees and leadership groups at FHS to meet the quality improvement needs of the organization. Identifies and validates evidence-based best practices in clinical practice and patient safety to guide clinical areas in performance improvement activities; researches nature/scope of impact on existing activities and makes appropriate recommendations through reports and presentations. Works with providers to interpret data trends in source and abstracted data; draws conclusions; summarizes findings that display compliance variations from regulatory standards. Maintains ongoing variance reports and updates managers/interested parties when significant trends appear in the data. Serves as a resource to internal departments for abstracted data-related questions. Provides informal instruction for internal customers to further quality improvement initiatives. Performs related duties as required.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Program Manager</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G27T6F5SXK0QMXG9T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G27T6F5SXK0QMXG9T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Modis is recruiting a Program Manager for a 4 month contract to hire job opportunity with our direct client to work in Chesterbrook PA area. The role of the Program Manager is to plan, execute, and finalize projects according to strict deadlines and within budget. This includes acquiring resources and coordinating the efforts of team members and third-party contractors or consultants in order to deliver projects according to plan. Will also define the project’s objectives and oversee quality control throughout its life cycle. Please apply quickly to learn more about this exciting opportunity~!~ Required Skills: Experience with financial and training projects preferred PMP Certification preferred Must also have excellent relationship building, interpersonal, presentation and communications skills • Will manage multiple projects and other project managers for the financial team and for the training work stream of a large program. • Develops, refines, validates and manages project plans to ensure on time and on budget delivery of major technology initiatives across the enterprise. • Responsible for utilizing project management methods, standards, project integration as well as the coordination of all internal and external resources required to complete assigned projects. • Provides timely and concise communications to functional leadership regarding project status and pending issues; analyzes processes and makes recommendations for optimizing resources and product delivery. • Develops project plans based on specifications provided by the Portfolio Management staff and manages effective execution of the initiatives. • Builds consensus among multiple process leads relative to project scope, task execution, staffing and issue resolution. • Brokers services within vendors on behalf of the business area represented. • Provides overall financial direction for the projects to manage the development of budgets, controls and measurements to monitor project progress. • Identifies potential risks within the project; proactively manages issues. • Participates in identifying project costs, resource allocation, project schedule changes and issue escalation. • Frequently interacts with IT staff including business area management, portfolio managers, vendors, consultants and other contractors. • Must be willing to travel up to 20% of the time. • Knowledge of computers to operative effectively with computer hardware such as general mainframe, midrange, network and desktop technologies; computer software includes application development lifecycle, MS Office Suite, Outlook. Clarity, HPQC tools experience is a plus. Phone screens first and then onsite interviews will be required. The position is funded to start ASAP. Client is an equal opportunity employer. Employment is contingent upon successful completion of the background investigation and pre-employment drug screen. Please email your resume for immediate consideration along with your rate expectations. Warm regards, Barb Heath Sr. Resource Development Manager Modis Tel 610.548.7317 Fax 610.548.2748 Rose Tree Corporate Center 1400 N. Providence Road, Building 2, Suite 5025 Media, PA (Email Address Withheld by Request) https://www.facebook.com/ModisPhiladelphia www.modis.com</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>User Interface/User Experience Designer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G840747G25MB7W7LP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G840747G25MB7W7LP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Top Three Skills: 1. UI/UX Design Experience 2. Adobe Creative Suite 3. Creation of Wireframes, concept flows, and visual designs Our client's Drilling &amp; Evaluation (D&amp;E) division is the core business driver behind Oilfield Services. We work with the software development group which develops programs, systems and applications that help our client's internal and external customers with day to day operations (analyze, interpret, quantify measure…..ect). They are currently setting a development standard for all future projects. They are changing the Architecture by dissociating the front end (UI) from the Business Logic which will essentially lower maintenance cost. Simultaneously, our client is replacing/rewriting all of their field acquisition systems from existing legacy technology to a .NET framework written in C# with a SQL Server backend. With the dissociation of the UI, they are looking to bring on a User Interface (UI) User Experience (UX) designer to assist with the technical/artistic design for the look and feel of all GUI's. This candidate's main responsibilities include: The ideal candidate must focus on detailed user flows and interaction models, They MUST have experience participating in user research and prototyping. Has developed specialist knowledge in two areas. This must be able to apply his/her knowledge/skills to a range of standard and non-standard activities. They must be able to apply leadership skills to influence design thinking. Assess the full requirements; identifies solutions to non-standard tasks/queries (organize tasks). Candidate is a resource of internal/external design knowledge and best practices. The candidate's work will be used to create visual and interaction designs within a multi-disciplinary team the results in new technology uses. This candidate will be tasked with some supervisory responsibilities in addition to own work assignments. They must demonstrate initiative &amp; contributes to problem solving. They must have excellent communication skills but also be able to work collaboratively with multiple disciplines. . PLEASE READ ADDITIONAL SKILLS/RESPONSIBILITIES: * Direct and execute visual design * Present process work and solutions, verbally and in writing * Spread knowledge throughout the organization * Implement methods and tools in the organization * Creation of wireframes, concept flows and visual designs * Implementation of robust user interface to multiple products * Use your exceptional communication skills to drive the creative process within department * Work with a multi-disciplinary team defining and prioritizing the features needed to create great user experiences with future disruptive technologies * Participate in Future Disruptions strategy development * Design and execute small and medium scale usability tests * Work with other visual designers to ensure compliance with key standards * Collaborate with Design and Conceptual team members to create working prototypes of design concepts * Participate in competitive analyses activities About TEKsystems: Join TEKsystems®, a leading IT staffing, IT talent management and IT services firm, and get your career on the fast track. We have more than 100 offices worldwide, and we partner with over 6,000 clients and place over 80,000 consultants per year. At TEKsystems, we seek to understand our consultants’ skills, goals and interests, allowing us to present targeted job opportunities on a contract, contract-to-hire or direct placement basis. TEKsystems' leadership in the market stems from our sincere and personal commitment to driving the success of our customers, consultants and each other.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Manager, Pharmacy Operations Project Managament (PHARMACIST) - Field Based</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G21974KL6GN2K3T5Z&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G21974KL6GN2K3T5Z&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: JOB TITLE: Mgr, Pharm Ops Proj Mgmt-P Sol At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our customers and communities. Function: Pharmacy Operations Family: Pharmacy Ops Project Mgmt What Pharmacy Ops Projects Mgmt contributes to Cardinal Health Pharmacy Operations and Account Management is responsible for strategic leadership direction, account management, and fiscal performance for assigned customers. Responsible for long-term relationship building and managing the success of the relationships What is expected of you for success in your role Manages professional employees and/or supervisors; may manage business support, technical or production staff Has accountability for managing financial resources Provides technical guidance to employees Develops processes and procedures to implement functional strategies Has in-depth expertise in own job family and knowledge of the related job families Applies expertise to improve effectiveness and provide guidance to employees in own area</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Director of Nursing - DON</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHN1CT6KM2M3YK6ZP45&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHN1CT6KM2M3YK6ZP45&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Covenant Care owns and operates skilled nursing facilities and a therapy services company. Our “family" includes over 8,500professionals running 53 skilled nursing facilities, 4 residential care facilities,and a therapy services company in 7 states. Managing risk has been critical to our success in the dynamic long-termcare industry. We have a strongcommitment to providing our residents with excellent care and service in apleasant, comfortable setting. CovenantCare is seeking a Director of Nursing for its Sunrise Skilled Nursing and Rehabilitation Center to lead and manage the Nursing Departmentand utilize available resources to provide quality, caring services to allresidents and patients, and achieve desired clinical and financial results. This position reports to our Executive Director. This home has a total of 99 beds. KeyExpectations: Achieve company and facility clinical indicators (pressure sores, weight loss, physical restraints, chemical restraints) Achieve facility goals for annual state survey (measured by tags and deficiencies) ensure nursing programs are provided for the facility (in-services) Facilitate and sustain effective IDT (Interdisciplinary Team) walking rounds per protocol Promote clinical and revenue improvements through effective participation in the PPS care management process Promote clinical and revenue improvements through Part B and other services (therapy) Effectively manage nursing hours PPD (Per Patient Day) compared to appropriate budget for actual census and mix (type of payer source for census) and state requirements. Ensures that all nursing documentation timely, accurate, and complete. Timely and effectively integrate all identified company, regional initiatives or best practices into operations. Comply with and supervise others to comply with CC business ethics, policies and procedures and all laws and regulations. Ensure that licensed staff completes clinical and medication administration competency skills checklist upon hire, annually, and as needed to maintain proficiencies. Maintain appropriate systems to manage all elements specific to Pharmacy process within CC expectations. Achieve high level of customer satisfaction for all attending and treating physicians. Timely and effectively integrate identified best practices into operations. Follows up on pertinent issues from consultant reports.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Compliance Specialist</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT4196XWRF8CC5KRT7&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT4196XWRF8CC5KRT7&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Responsibilities will include: ARCOS reporting DEA reconciliation DEA reporting, including but not limited to, Form 41, Form 106, Form 222 ”Good Faith Inquiry” reporting Conducting year-end ARCOS inventory Controlled Substance Ordering System (CSOS) Monitoring quota requests and suspicious orders Reverse distribution of controlled substances Maintaining state and federal licenses Conducting internal DEA audits DEA technical support as needed</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Process Control Engineer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR6L86P41MSSDH37MB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR6L86P41MSSDH37MB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Duties and responsibilities: Support existing custom applications and development of new applications. This will include computer programming and some system administration skills. Use computers and PLC's to control process equipment used in the production and processing of steel. Analyze problems to find root cause. Involves some user contact to diagnose the problem. Willing to respond to trouble calls on a 24/7 basis.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Downtown OTR Reporter</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H1DL6YG1G9XNQM38D&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H1DL6YG1G9XNQM38D&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Cincinnati.com and The Enquirer are searching for a Reporter to join our newsroom. As a Downtown and OTR Reporter: 100% of your focus is the 25-45 audience. You know more about Downtown and OTR – the decision makers, what’s coming next, what's opening and closing, the urban pioneers – than any other media. You get access to the key players unlike any other media. You are the person that people follow if they want to know what’s important in this area. You are competitive; you rarely get beat. You do rich stories showing people striving &amp; struggling to make their community better. You write with a strong sense of place, with details and reporting that are relatable beyond that neighborhood. You break news on what is important to your audience as well as aggregate content by the dining and development and other reporters. You are an excellent storyteller. You are comfortable with voice -- you bring your unique voice to all your stories, social media, video appearances and public appearances. You are comfortable sharing your personality that helps 25-45-year-olds create a personal connection to you. You engage your audience consistently throughout the week -- you build a true community and relationship around your coverage. You continually initiate new techniques in your coverage to meet the interests and needs of 25-45 year olds. You work with your advertising partner to grow and monetize the 25-45 audience Required Skills + Abilities Bachelor's in Communications, Journalism or equivalent in experience and education. Ability to build coalitions around evolving needs. Minimum 3-5 years in the journalism field Effective communicator; able to get along with diverse personalities. Deep understanding of and curiosity about competition for our customers' time and money. Self-motivation and self-direction. Industry knowledge. Able to multi-task and excel under intense deadline pressure in a rapidly changing environment. Knows how to use time efficiently in a 24-hour news environment. Works collaboratively within a cross-functional environment. Must embrace peer-to-peer training, as a both a teacher and student. Applies innovative, creative thinking to support the company’s goals. Writing, spelling, grammar, AP and local style. Knowledge of media law and Principles of Ethical Conduct. Pacing: Signature piece every month. In-depth take/insight on the news, weekly. Breaking news through the week. Typical hours: varies About Us Gannett Co., Inc. (NYSE: GCI) is an international media and marketing solutions company that informs and engages more than 100 million people every month through its powerful network of broadcast, digital, mobile and publishing properties. Our portfolio of trusted brands offers marketers unmatched local-to-national reach and customizable, innovative marketing solutions across any platform. Gannett is committed to connecting people – and the companies who want to reach them – with their interests and communities. For more information, visit www.gannett.com. Gannett employees are hired, promoted and rewarded on the basis of talent, performance and dedication. We cannot afford to deprive the company of capable people and will not allow harassment or discrimination based on race, creed, color, religion, national origin, sex, age, sexual orientation, marital status, ancestry, disability or veteran status. Gannett Co., Inc. is a proud equal opportunity employer</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Manager in Training</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS7HW6TJF55LN972ZP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS7HW6TJF55LN972ZP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: We are seeking high-energy, positive leaders with a documented track record of success in growing people, sales, revenues and profit in a retail environment. We work hard and have fun, and we drive to be the best so we are seeking only the best. If you can answer "YES" to all of the following questions we want to speak to you! 1) Do you have a proven track record with inside and outside Sales &amp; Marketing? 2) Can you manage 5 or more people on a daily basis and build a strong successful team? 3) Are you a leader with the ability to inspire perfection among your peers and associates? 4) Are you comfortable working on a daily basis with customers, selling, resolving problems, and providing the BEST customer service in our industry? If you can answer YES to all of the above questions please submit your resume for these postions. Requirements Responsibilities: Responsible for the growth and retention of customers Continuously develop, train and manage employees Responsible for setting and attaining goals Manage expired customer agreements Explore and react to profitable revenue opportunities within the store Take a visible role in representing Aaron's in the local community We Offer: Extensive Training Proframs through Aaron's E-University Five day work week Sundays off! And another day during the week Hourly wage plus bonus and commission Medical, Dental, Vision &amp; Life Insurance Benefits Matched 401K plan after 1 year Paid Vacation Paid Holidays Sick Pay Employee purchase discounts Referral program</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Business Analyst</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT70Z6BC26H53YDQYH&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT70Z6BC26H53YDQYH&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Sales Business Analyst Job Description Radio Flyer holds a special place in people's hearts. This is true because Radio Flyer transports people to a happy time, to the best parts of childhood, a time when anything was possible. For over 95 years, our company has produced children's products that bring smiles and create warm memories that last a lifetime and the Radio Flyer brand has become an American icon. Beyond our classic Little Red Wagon™, today Radio Flyer produces tricycles, scooters, wagons, and many other ride-ons that have fueled our growth and success. Radio Flyer is a recognized leader in the toy industry, headquartered in Chicago - headed by Robert Pasin, grandson of the company founder. Radio Flyer has consistently been recognized as a top workplace and received numerous awards such as, Best Places to Work in Illinois, Wall Street Journal’s Top Small Workplaces, Chicago’s 101 Best and Brightest Companies to Work For and Crain’s Best Places to Work. Having fun at Radio Flyer isn’t just another perk, it’s a job requirement! We are committed to a culture that embraces positive energy, achieves results and drives business growth. At Radio Flyer we live by the Little Red Rule, “Every time we touch people's lives, they will feel great about Radio Flyer!" To learn more about our company, please visit our website at: www.radioflyer.com . Opportunity: This position will play a key role in the continued growth and success of the company. The qualified candidate will work with the sales and marketing organization to conduct the analysis required to grow our top accounts. The required skill set will include successful product forecasting, order planning, POS analysis, running reports to support the National Account Managers in developing a growth plan for the account. We will look to this person to partner with our National Account Manager in developing our annual business plan with our retailers, work with finance to ensure the timing and processing of key orders, work with our Operations team to manage the planning with our suppliers and work directly with the retailer to manage the inventory levels of our products, work closely with these key accounts to process orders, manage timing of these orders to support daily replenishment or key promotions. Specific responsibilities include: Forecasting within + / - 20% accuracy Create 12 month promotional plans Build the 12 month budget by SKU and promotion Work closely with the National Account Manager to develop an account plan that drives growth Work with Finance to manage the processing of account orders Manage the details of the Customer Program – deductions, coop, accruals, mark downs Manage the annual pricing for key accounts, including temporary price cuts and promotional buys Develop relationships with key account forecasting and inventory planning teams to assist in managing our inventory levels to optimize rate of sale</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Maintenance Technician</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS6LZ6XHPF70S2W329&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS6LZ6XHPF70S2W329&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: PeopleShare in Horsham, PA is seeking experienced Maintenance Technicians with experience in the manufacturing industry for an excellent temp-hire opportunity in the Montgomeryville, PA area ! To maintain and repair all production machinery and supporting equipment. In addition to maintenance, the tech’s should be available to help teams in production by covering machines, when needed. 70% of time: Repair or maintain all production equipment with the least amount of interface and delay with normal operations. Testing of faulty equipment using precision test apparatus. Applies knowledge of functional operation of electrical, electronic, mechanical, hydraulic, pneumatic, and vacuum systems to perform complex diagnostics to determine the root cause of malfunctions and execute timely repairs of equipment. Repairs or replaces defective parts and wiring and adjusts mechanical parts using hand, bench, power tools, soldering iron, and/or torch. Aligns, adjusts, and calibrates according to specifications. Ability to troubleshoot and maintain industrial electronic process automated equipment. Perform electrical and mechanical troubleshooting, repair, and testing of in-house lasers, text fixtures, and associated equipment to maintain equipment in optimal operating condition. Determine the nature of a production problem; evaluate resources, coordinate with available personnel to achieve a desirable outcome, while assigned as the mechanic on call. Ensure a timely response, repair, and solution to equipment related issues, and take action to solve problems, when they are encountered, by teaming with other organizations/individuals to ensure customer satisfaction. Contribute to the measurable metric standards for the organization in the area of equipment downtime, equipment utilization, personnel training, organization value to company, and any other metrics determined helpful to ensure a world-class organization. Comply with all pertinent safety &amp; housekeeping instructions and procedures, fully understanding Material Safety Data Sheets and OSHA’s Hazard communication system. Including chemical spill removal as required, and Fire Extinguisher training &amp; usage Under minimal supervision, will maintain, troubleshoot, repair, install, and rebuild production and facilities equipment. The EM Tech will have shift responsibility for maintenance and calibration of microprocessor based control equipment, general instrumentation, and electrical control systems to carry-out first line diagnostic, troubleshooting, and maintenance work, ability to read and understand relay logic and schematic diagrams, perform tests, and calibration procedures using test equipment and instrumentation. The EM Tech will frequently work under pressure to diagnose problems Will work on assignments that are routine and not routine in nature where ability to recognize deviation from accepted practice is required and expected. Will be required to investigate the root-cause of issues and provide information to Engineers and Project Managers. Technicians are involved in equipment programming adjustments, equipment repair, equipment/tooling setup, and programming, as well assisting team operators in resolving production problems. 25% of time Locate and order spare parts – goal to establish a supply chain that is faster and cheaper than OEM. Recommend stocking of critical items as spare parts (and material) for equipment servicing. Enter and retrieve data for parts and maintenance tasks as required Create and modify simple PLC programs. Troubleshoot and repair numerous complex electronics systems Perform light fabrication of simple electro-mechanical prototype systems, and structural components and tools, as needed Perform scheduled and unscheduled maintenance on lasers, test fixtures, and associated test equipment: including troubleshooting, repairing, and ordering parts to maintain equipment in optimal operating condition. Additionally, assist in design and development of cutting edge technologies in support of the product portfolio. Provides technical expertise to lower skilled employees within organization Carryout preventative maintenance per written procedures as outlined by the maintenance schedule. Provide technical expertise and skills to ensure continuous improvement of the Preventative Maintenance Program Assist in the development of process documentation, equipment maintenance standards, BOMs, and detailed parts breakdowns. Documenting and maintaining prototype construction, test data, and related documentation Assisting in the research and evaluation of new electronic/mechanical components Proper documentation of work performed, part used, and time sheets as required. Assist in operator training, related to equipment setup and maintenance. Perform machining requirements, which include the proper use of lathes, mills, surface grinders, drill press, welding and brazing equipment, and other machine shop related practices. Fabrication, assembly and installation of tooling and fixturing from drawings. Will be assigned to special projects working under descriptive instructions only, including new installations, retrofits and upgrades. 5% or less of time Other duties – operate Fork Truck, Load PVC scrap truck; remove trash, escort outside service technicians. Connect PC to a machine interface and transfer an associated program Installation and movement of machines while observing all requirements of lock-out/tag-out policies and procedures Snow removal as required Will provide other engineering and basic facility related support functions as required. This may include plumbing, painting, and general support functions. Developing written documentation of technical assembly, test, and setup processes Additional duties include maintenance &amp; housekeeping of shop area, tools, and materials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Activities Coordinator</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL09F6JDSGX23J9HHQ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL09F6JDSGX23J9HHQ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Cypress Springs is an Alzheimer’s and Memory Support Residence that just celebrated its 3-year anniversary! We are currently seeking an energetic full-time/part-time, Activities Coordinator for our community. Essential Functions: Assist Program Director in planning and providing activities that support and maintain the residents’ quality of life, and that meet state requirements for addressing the residents’ social, physical, spiritual and mental health. Plans, coordinates and implements active and passive activities in both the North and South Courts to address the needs of residents with varying abilities. Provides supportive activities in a comfortable environment to residents who are not able to tolerate stimulation of a group program. Working Conditions: Able to work full-time or part-time as agreed upon with Program Director, with weekend work required Ability to travel locally if necessary, to purchase supplies and participate in resident outings .</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Entry Level  Assemblers Needed - Manufacturing Company in Beaverton, OR</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F2V75YQJJ7CYFF4WC&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F2V75YQJJ7CYFF4WC&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Kelly Services offers more opportunities at Fortune 500 companies than any other staffing provider! You have talent, ambition and skills, now is your time to achieve something more with us. We have partnered with a Leading Manufacturer of Optics products on Assembly positions with the following job description: Performs routine and repetitive assembly operations in the production of precision optics utilizing drawings, diagrams, and written instructions. May use standard shop hand and power tools.* Consistently demonstrate and maintain established production and quality levels in assigned work areas where proficiency has been established.* Visually inspect component parts for contamination or damage.* Clean or remove dirt, dust, grease, adhesives or other contaminates from component parts using established procedures.* Manipulate and install small parts and pieces to assemble sub-assemblies and component parts into finished product in accordance with established procedures. This may include o-rings, cam-tubes, pivot tubes, erector springs, adjustments, dials, caps, drive pins, wavy washers, step-washers, reticles (electroform), main-tubes, objective &amp; eyepiece (build), lenses, b-rings, eye-shells, circuit boards, mirror (prep), armor and stop-nuts.* Use common and specialized hand tools and assembly fixtures including items such as torque wrenches, comparators, water tester, and nitrogen filler. Use all equipment properly and in a safe manner.* Follow all work area procedures and documented processes to insure product meets standards.* Maintain work area cleanliness and organization for increase efficiency, accuracy and quality.* Ensure work meets the area defect acceptance limitations using the established quality standards and specifications.* Operate grease and or glue dispensers per work instructions and change grease brushes and fixtures as needed.* Verify correct parts, torques, adhesive and lubricant applications per work instructions.* Check for defects using drawings, specifications and work instructions; identify defect codes and properly tag and record the defect.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Audit/Inventory Control</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H2XL7983FSNWS3HHF&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H2XL7983FSNWS3HHF&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Our client, a luxury goods company, is seeking a Sales Audit/Inventory temp to conduct a physical inventory at their warehouse. This assignment will only be for a few days in mid-December. Job Responsibilities Include: Aids in taking inventory of all warehouse materials Count large units of merchandise Perform additional duties as assigned Job Requirements: MUST have experience with scanning inventory Ability to lift up to 50 lbs Must be good with numbers Please submit your resume with "Sales Audit/Inventory" in the subject for consideration. While PCG appreciates all applicants, only those qualified will be contacted. Thank you for your application. We look forward to hearing from you!</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Executive Assistant/ Project Administrator</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV1TF6PXYL31Z1HVDD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV1TF6PXYL31Z1HVDD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: We are recruiting for a polished and experienced Executive Assistant to provide support a very busy executive and the department employees for a large organization is Sacramento. Provide support to the Senior Executives and at times support other partnering company Executives as needed. SKILLS: Managing and coordinating heavy calendar. Assists key executives make consistent decisions by providing extensive and varied administrative support. Arranges corporate travel and meetings by developing itineraries and agendas; scheduling all meeting accommodations. Coordinates regular Conference Calls and Webinars for the executive and others who will be attending the meeting. Completes projects and special assignments by establishing objectives; determining priorities; managing time; gaining cooperation of others; monitoring progress; problem-solving; making adjustments to plans. Prepares in-depth PowerPoint Presentations for Executive Meetings and Conferences. Must be able to work on complex administrative projects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Metal Technician- Auto Body</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR3HN6HVGP14HDJVDK&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR3HN6HVGP14HDJVDK&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: *****Body Shop Metal Technician***** Are you ready to make a change? Are you being held back from achieving your full potential at your current job? We would like to invite you to join our great Team! Schaller Auto Body , one of Connecticut's premiere high volume facilities is looking for quality technicians. New state of the art, air conditioned facility, great working conditions and the latest tools with which you can be very productive and achieve what you are really worth. Schaller's has a complete benefit package to suit all your needs. Call for a personal interview call Bruce@ (860) 826-2030 or email Bruce at</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Supervisor Process Engineering</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JYR2VW5YC8JG9V5TZKY&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JYR2VW5YC8JG9V5TZKY&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Title: Process Engineering Supervisor Location: Paris, Illinois North American Lighting (NAL) , a member of the Japan-based Koito family of companies, is a leading manufacturer of automotive lighting products. Together we form a cohesive network bringing Koito technology to people around the world. This global presence not only helps answer customer needs and facilitates stable product supply, but gives us unique strengths in capitalizing on new opportunities worldwide. North American Lighting (NAL) currently has an opportunity for a Process Engineering Supervisor to be located at our facility in Paris, IL! As the Supervisor - Process Engineering at our Corporate Headquarters facility in Paris, IL., you will utilize your experience and talents to supervise and coordinate the activities of a team of process engineers who provide engineering and development support in the areas of new materials and processes, equipment, design guidelines, and material performance for new automotive lighting products and future material-related development projects Essential Duties and Responsibilities Coordinates and oversees the development of new material and process-related technologies, and makes recommendations to NAL management Supervises and coordinates the activities of a team of process engineers, and assigns the work-load to best achieve project objectives and required timing Ensures that NAL material, process, and design specifications are established and maintained Assists Process Engineers in the following areas: Analyzing and resolving issues requiring management input Evaluates and improves materials and processes corporate-wide in order to add value by: Lowering material costs Increasing processing efficiency Improving product value with customers Satisfy new customer requirements Required Skills Bachelor's Degree in Engineering, Material Science, or a related technicaldiscipline 6 to 8 years of experience in a process related positionin the areas of material selection, testing, implementation, and process, including 2 years of experience in a supervisory or lead role Competencies Knowledge and understanding of standards — such as Society of Automotive Engineers (SAE) and/or American Standard Technical Methods (ASTM) Technical writing and presentation skills Problem solving and data analysis Organization and planning Leadership and communications skills Interpersonal relations – confidently interact with individuals at all levels of authority</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Outside Sales Representative (Home Office)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR2MP69R244F8HVNB6&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR2MP69R244F8HVNB6&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Outside Sales Representative Our client is a successful international manufacturing company that is currently seeking an experienced Outside Sales Representative to join their team. We are looking for an individual with excellent interpersonal, organization and communication skills. THis position covers North Carolina and SOuth Carolina territories, and based from a home office. If you are interested in utilizing your skills and experience with a great company, apply today!</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Auto Parts Sales / Automotive Parts Advisor / Ford Parts Counter Sales</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP6WX6CNQD0MTKYY07&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP6WX6CNQD0MTKYY07&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Parts Advisors / Parts Counter HIGH VOLUME SHOP - HEALTH - DENTAL - VISION - 401K Shouldn’t you be working as an Automotive Parts Advisor / Parts Counterperson for a dealership that PAYS YOU what you’re worth? Isn’t it time you took your Parts Advisor career further? Job Responsibilities Parts Advisors sell parts to meet monthly forecasts Parts Advisors Issue parts and accessories to mechanics from the parts counter. Parts Advisors Solicit customers for parts and accessories sales using phone, direct mail, etc. Provide delivery service of orders using parts truck. Display seasonal parts and accessories in an attractive manner. Control files, reference books, and other paperwork at the parts counter Maintain customer back order file. Maintain master parts and price book. Receive original and duplicate copies of repair orders from dispatcher and place in order file. Join our automotive parts sales team today - apply now!</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Maintenance Manager</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL6HD68ZNLBTXYVRV7&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL6HD68ZNLBTXYVRV7&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: An international manufacturer of automotive components near Augusta, GA is looking for a Maintenance Manager to lead the Maintenance Department for a medium-sized plant. There are 15-25 Maintenance Mechanics and Maintenance Technicians at this plant. The Maintenance Manager will be involved in both mechanical and electrical maintenance. His or her responsibilities will include direct supervision of salaried employees and hourly employees, troubleshooting the repair of production and support equipment, leading plant modification and equipment installation projects. The Maintenance Manager must be familiar with mechanical, electrical, hydraulic and pneumatic systems. He or she must also be familiar with TPM, OEE and equipment calibration. Candidates for Maintenance Manager will need a Bachelors degree from an accredited university, along with at least 10 years of recent maintenance experience in a busy manufacturing plant. At least 3 years of supervisory experience is required. Excellent communication, organizational and leadership skills are absolutely required for this position. Overnight travel is expected to be minimal. Visa sponsorship is not available for this position. There is a strong preference for local (GA, SC) candidates. This company offers excellent benefits. Candidates with a stable work record, who meet the above requirements, should email your resume to .</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Wheelchair Attendant / Baggage Handler</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP7TW6458L5MNNGTFT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP7TW6458L5MNNGTFT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Gateway Frontline Services is hiring for multiple positions at our Las Vegas McCarran Airport Gateway Frontline Services partners with the airlines in McCarran airport to provide various front line services to their passengers. Our mission is Excellence. One relationship at a time. At Gateway Frontline Services, we know your career is an investment in your future. As we continue to grow, our employees benefit by growing with us. Our diverse team is full of opportunities to develop while being part of a dynamic, fast-paced team. Gateway Frontline Services is currently looking for driven, motivated customer service experts eager to help us achieve our mission. Gateway Frontline Services are hiring for the following positions: Wheelchair Attendant Provides assistance to passengers traveling in wheelchairs to and from their departure or arrival gates Assists passengers with luggage to their vehicles, taxi, parking shuttle stations, and rental car stations Services may require assisting passengers through security and gathering wheelchair equipment from parking areas, baggage claim, and other airline gate areas Wheelchair attendants must maintain a friendly and positive attitude and always be attentive to each passenger’s needs Wheelchair attendant position entails and Other duties as assigned Baggage Handler Assists airlines with baggage transportation from one location to another Handles oversized baggage and transports to proper conveyor belt Requires the use of caution when handling passenger bags Reports any required maintenance to manager May be requested to perform other duties as assigned based on manager’s needs or airline activity</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Public Works &amp; Planning Sr. Project Director</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H8096W6ZYHFTKDGFV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H8096W6ZYHFTKDGFV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Atkins has been providing infrastructure planning, engineering, construction, environmental consulting, urban planning, architecture, and program management services to public and private clients across the United States for more than 50 years. Globally, Atkins is the largest UK-based engineering and design consultancy and the world's 11th largest design firm with nearly 18,000 employees worldwide. We have the depth and breadth of expertise to respond to the most technically challenging and time-critical infrastructure projects and the urgent transition to a low-carbon economy. At Atkins, we offer our employees more than just a job; we offer an opportunity to shape the world for generations to come through innovative and sound design. As the official engineer of the 2012 London Olympics, few companies can rival the size and diversity of our projects. Whether it’s the concept for a new skyscraper, the upgrade of a rail network, the modeling of a flood defense system or the improvement of a management process, we plan, design and enable solutions. Atkins seeks an energetic, highly motivated, detail-oriented, self-starter to join our San Diego staff as a Public Works &amp; Planning Sr. Project Director. MAJOR FUNCTION/ROLE: Under general direction, manages complex and unconventional technology or delivery systems for a single significant project within a defined technical specialty. Projects typically involve high levels of regulatory agency involvement or very complex technical requirements. Typical projects might include construction management engagements, significant design-build or design-build-operate-maintain undertakings, major and unique structures, major wastewater treatment facilities, etc. Provides leadership, direction, and technical guidance to senior project managers and project managers within assigned area of responsibility to ensure that quality management and technical services are provided to clients and that operating performance targets are met. Mentors senior project managers and project managers associated with sophisticated and unconventional projects. Projects of this magnitude generally involve net revenues totaling between $2.5 million to $5 million annually and require specialized expertise. JOB DUTIES: Management assignments typically involve large, multi-discipline assignments, including unconventional or complex projects made up of 1 or 2 highly sophisticated and specialized technical components generating annual net revenue between $2.5 million to $5 million annually. Atkins offers its employees a robust rewards package which includes: a competitive salary; a broad benefits package including medical/RX, dental, vision, life, disability, legal, hospitalization and other valuable voluntary options; generous time-off programs; flexible work schedules; 401(k) with employer match; professional and career development opportunities through our corporate university, as well as a highly-regarded tuition reimbursement program; and an unmatched culture focused on client-service, quality, and tireless pursuit of excellence in all we do. Atkins is an equal opportunity, drug-free employer committed to diversity in the workplace.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Automotive Technicians Needed</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHQ71V6X60KVS8S9NPL&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHQ71V6X60KVS8S9NPL&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job Responsibilities Confer with customers or service advisors to obtain descriptions of vehicle problems, and to discuss work to be performed and future repair requirements. Test-drive vehicles, and test components and systems, using diagnostic tools and special service equipment. Perform quality inspections of vehicle repairs prior to returning the vehicle to the customer Diagnose, maintain, and repair vehicle automotive systems including engine, transmission, electrical, steering, suspension, braking, air conditioning, etc Communicate directly with the service advisor so that customers can be informed if any additional service is needed. Providing an estimate of time needed for additional repairs. Execute repairs under warranty to manufacturer specifications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Benefits Assistant</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS65B6HH61DTSS4X4F&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS65B6HH61DTSS4X4F&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Benefits Assistant The overall purpose of the Administrative Assistant to Director of Benefits is to perform various clerical duties for the Employee Benefits Department. Confidentiality is necessary in all aspects of the position. Essential Functions • Must be familiar with all benefits programs, eligibility periods, and answer all employee/facility questions and concerns. • The department is responsible for enrolling, terminating, changing employee’s coverage, self-billing, and distribution of materials. • Audit and process daily payroll changes report. • Data entry and maintenance in online benefit administration system. • Process all requests for coverage cancellations and terminations as needed. • Process incoming mail on a daily basis • Copying of materials pertinent to various employees’ insurance programs for distribution (new employee packets, instructional materials, etc.) • Answer questions regarding insurance benefits offered by the company, specific programs in which individual employees are enrolled, FMLA and other leaves, COBRA. • Audit and process daily termination report • Assist in sending hire packets, writing up double deductions and reimbursements for employees when necessary. • Filing and maintaining employee benefit files. • Attorney General Notices • Maintains compliance with requirements in compliance program/plan.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Administrative Assistant</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP77Z72NPJ62V9HYPQ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP77Z72NPJ62V9HYPQ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: SUMMARY: Provides general office and secretarial/clerical functions, marketing support, and proposal preparation support by performing the following duties. Reports directly to the Senior Structural Engineer of the Lexington, KY office. ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES include the following. Other duties may be assigned. Assists department personnel in project and department administration and coordination as requested. Maintains project related contract files and assists with project invoicing. Assists the Senior Structural Engineer in the preparation of proposals. Works with and supports project team. Produces letters, memos and correspondence on engineering topics such as, legal description and easements, engineering agreements, reports, studies, ads, proposals, specifications, tables, contracts, forms and all other business typing as requested by department personnel. Files correspondence and other records. Makes copies of correspondence or other printed matter. Assembles engineering reports. Prepares outgoing mail. Assists in making travel, conference, seminar and client meeting arrangements. Participates in departmental telecommunications. Assists in office overflow work with other Administrative Assistants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Accounts Payable</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J8C3PH78CMWF0QNVHV3&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J8C3PH78CMWF0QNVHV3&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: The H&amp;K Group, A Family of Companies, the fastest growing Heavy Highway Site Contracting Company seeks an Accounts Payable person for it's Corporate Office located in Skippack, PA. Founded in 1968, the Company has continued to grow and has expanded it's operation to include quarries, site contracting companies, asphalt plants, concrete plants and lock and paver plants. With over 75 locations, these companies span across the Eastern half of PA and into NJ, DE and MD. The H&amp;K Group is a safety conscious, drug free, alcohol free work environment. Pre-employment drug testing is required. No provision for relocation. Local candidates preferred. Competitive wages and benefits. Tuition Reimbursement (EOE)</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Civil Engineer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H5V464DVL00X41PHK&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H5V464DVL00X41PHK&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Seeking a Process Mechanical CAD Engineer/Designer to work alongside staff Engineers in the design and production of contract documents for various water and wastewater projects. * Prepare plan, section and detail drawings for various chemical and process systems * Coordinate with the other disciplines * Ensure drawing compliance with company and client CAD standards and styles 2nd opening for a candidate with 10+ years of experience, to work alongside Staff Engineers in the design and production of contract documents for water/wastewater projects Will coordinate w the other disciplines and provide solutions to conflicts Will ensure drawing compliance with company and client CAD standards and styles Create, manage and supervise production of contract drawing submittals -2 IMMEDIATE OPENINGS! -WE ALSO HAVE OPENINGS IN THE ENVIRONMENTAL, GEOTECHNICAL, AND STRUCTURAL ENGINEERING FIELDS, AS WELL AS CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT AND ARCHITECTURE -PAY IS BASED ON EXPERIENCE About Aerotek: Aerotek, headquartered in Hanover, Md., is a leading provider of technical, professional and industrial staffing services. Established in 1983, Aerotek is an operating company of Allegis Group, the largest provider of staffing services in the U.S. Aerotek operates a network of more than 200 non-franchised offices throughout the U.S., Canada and Europe. For more information, visit aerotek.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Tool and Die Maker / Toolmaker</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM6YF62GPK6QCJPB6Q&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM6YF62GPK6QCJPB6Q&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Wood-Mizer is hiring a direct, full-time Tool and Die Maker / Toolmaker. Tool and Die Maker / Toolmaker will get full benefits - medical, vision and dental insurance, 401K, 401K matching, health club reimbursement, tuition reimbursement, and generous vacation! Tool and Die Maker / Toolmaker Essential Functions of the Job: • Read prints and produce prototype parts and assemblies from prints or sketches. • Develop, construct and alter a wide variety of jigs, fixtures and gauges. • Perform assignments that range from the use of ordinary tool room operations to work involving accurate and extremely close tolerances. • Produce prototype units or tools to print specifications. • Design and produce tooling from parts prints • Perform testing and document results • Operate any machine in the tool room such as mills, laths, drill presses • Expertly use various gauges and measuring instruments. • Assist development engineering with process improvements. Tool and Die Maker / Toolmaker Peripheral Functions of the Job: • Perform other duties according to supervisor's instructions. • Assist manufacturing with process improvements • Clean work area. • Able to wire weld • Able to use torch or plasma cutter</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Body Shop Tech</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP4TY6ML2MFZ5KR9NT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP4TY6ML2MFZ5KR9NT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Body Shop Tech Be a part of one of the most important teams in the dealership - The service department! State-of-the-art equipment and career advancement join our service department as our Body Shop Tech. Apply Today! Meet and greet customers, help making insurance claims and prepare estimates/photos for upload and approval. Knowledge of most major Insurance Direct Repair Program protocols, including Geico, State Farm, and Nationwide. Have the ability to upload estimates/images that meet those standards. Maintain contact with customer while vehicle is in the repair process, maintaining communication regarding status of repair. Prepare and submit Warranty Claims Reconcile and prepare for invoicing final invoices that match approved estimates. Contact owner well in advance of completion to communicate when they can expect the repair to be completed. Body Shop Tech Qualifications: 5 Years Experience Preferred - on all makes and models. I-Car, CCC1, Reynolds, Autex or other industry training history a plus Prefer candidate to be fluent in CCC Pathways and Reynolds Systems Must have verifiable relationships with major insurance DRP programs. Team oriented, flexible and focused on maintaining a high level of Customer Service. Benefits: Great Compensation 401K Savings Plan Health Insurance Paid Vacation Paid Training It's time to make the most important move of your career, Apply Now! Submit your resume Or Call Ali at 301-595-2403 to set up an interview. We are an equal opportunity employer and a drug free workplace. All applicants must be able to demonstrate ability to pass pre-employment testing to include background checks, MVR, drug test, credit report, and valid driver license.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Truck Driver Student</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F3C96D0Z45HCCBM7T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F3C96D0Z45HCCBM7T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job Summary: At Con-way, our driver job is not just behind the wheel. If you are looking to drive our business and not just our trucks, Con-way could be a good fit for you. Our drivers not only deliver freight and final goods to our service centers and customers' businesses safely, efficiently and free from damage, but they are also involved in unloading and distributing the freight as well. A Con-way driver is also a key part of our customer service team, as they frequently interface with customers, forging our relationship with them and driving future business. The Con-way Freight (LTL) Driver Sales Representative Student (DSR Student)Program is an intensive twelve module training program consisting of classroom education and hands on driving experience. The DSR Student will work as a dock worker for a minimum of 30 days prior to the start of classroom training. There is up to 90 days of classroom training in the program. If successfully completed, the DSR Student will be eligible to test to obtain a Commercial Drivers License with hazardous materials endorsements and doubles/triples endorsements, and upon meeting all other company requirements the DSR Student may be eligible to be offered a Driver/Sales Representative position. Description of Essential Job Functions: Available to work a variety of shifts, including days, evenings, nights and weekends. Ability to work the designated shift prior to or following a 4 hour unpaid classroom training session. Unload &amp; load freight off/on trailers; lift freight &amp; other objects of various shapes, sizes &amp; weights (up to 50 lbs frequently &amp; greater than 75 lbs occasionally); safely operate heavy equipment; move &amp; position a converter dolly with an average weight/pull force of approximately 128 lbs; safely climb in and out of a tractor cab &amp; trailer; sit for extended periods of time in a truck tractor and/or forklift; safely walk &amp; stand for extended periods of time on various surfaces that may be uneven or slippery; when required and under supervision, safely operate a tractor/trailer combination, in all types of weather, while safely transporting hazardous/non-hazardous materials; and safely walk, reach (including above your head), bend, climb, push, pull, twist, squat &amp; kneel as necessary to perform the job duties. Under supervision, safely operate tractor-trailer combination, including doubles (and triples, where applicable) and perform vehicle inspections required under section 396.13 of the Federal Motor Carriers Safety Regulations. Obtain a Class A CDL permit and within 90 days obtain a Class A CDL with Hazardous Materials and Doubles/Triples endorsements. Maintain records in accordance with Federal Motor Carrier Safety Regulations ( FMCSR), Department of Transportation (DOT), and company policies as required. Verify and complete required documentation and reports. Ability to handle hazardous materials. Adhere to company safety policies. Frequent contact with service center personnel in a fast-paced and deadline oriented environment. Safely work in adverse weather conditions. Perform other duties as assigned. Prompt, daily attendance at assigned work location.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Staff Auditor</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL8807497XWJS9HDDB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL8807497XWJS9HDDB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Under the direction of the Internal Audit Seniors, Managers, and Director, the individual will be responsible to assist in the execution of the JM Family Enterprises, Inc. audit plan. Responsibilities include, but are not limited to: • Assist in planning and conducting audits with the audit seniors and Audit Manager and according to internal audit procedures. This includes: o Assist in conducting walkthrough procedures of key processes. o Conduct detail testing of key processes and controls. o Providing an independent and objective evaluation of internal controls, business processes, policies and procedures, as result of testing, etc. o Documenting test work and audit findings with associated business risks and making recommendations to enhance internal controls and /or identify opportunities for improved efficiencies. o Assist in preparing audit reports that summarize and rank the audit findings and recommendations as well as associated business risks. o Obtaining responses from auditee to the audit findings and ensuring the responses address the identified control/process deficiencies. o Work with other auditors and coordinating audits/projects, as assigned, to ensure timely completion. o Performing follow-up with the auditee to ensure all agreed to actions have been completed. • Prepare and present audit findings and recommendations to audit senior, Audit Manager, auditees, and CFO where applicable. • Ability to work on multiple concurrent audits and projects, and compliance related activities, as requested.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanker Driver (CDL Driver)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS69J6M2QJ6YZW83M2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS69J6M2QJ6YZW83M2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Tanker Driver Regional and Local Routes Available in Winder “If you take care of Groendyke, Groendyke will take care of you. They pay attention to details and the small things, like my birthday and my family. That matters." As a Tanker Driver , your responsibilities will include regional and local driving responsibilities of hauling, handling and transportation of liquid or bulk commodities, including hazardous materials. Our people enjoy one of the best benefit packages in the industry . Groendyke Transport will provide you with excellent pay rates, comprehensive benefits and ongoing training to keep you safely driving far into the future. Tanker Driver - We offer: Competitive Compensation of $65,000 Constantly updating our truck fleet &amp; safety equipment Paid Vacation &amp; Holidays Uniforms Medical, Dental and Vision Life and Short-term Disability Insurance 401(k) plan and company match quarterly safety incentive plan</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketing Coordinator</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB75M16JDR8XR18G6S2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB75M16JDR8XR18G6S2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job is located in North Richland Hills, TX. Position Summary Are you a dreamer with an undeniable passion for utilizing your talents to engage customers? Someone who thrives on endless possibility and opportunity while enjoying stability and support and believes that coming to work should offer them excitement and the ability to have an immediate impact. Are you looking for a place to become part of a team of gifted innovators who value a collaborative and strategic atmosphere in order to rapidly and directly influence the way consumers shop for health and supplemental protection as they navigate the uncharted reform marketplace? Based in the Dallas-Fort Worth metropolitan area, HealthMarkets is a privately owned holding company focused on serving the insurance needs of individuals, families and small business through our subsidiary insurance companies; and we are embarking on an initiative to build on our vast nationwide agent network by adding an innovative and consumer-centric web-based shopping experience to deliver our portfolio of products. Our already vast network of agents and carrier partners, coupled with half a million policies already sold, places us in the unique position to offer consumers an unprecedented shopping experience. At HealthMarkets, consumers will be in the driver’s seat – able to compare and buy insurance products online, through our trusted local agents, or in any combination they choose. The consumer has the choice and we need you to help us deliver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>LR06 - Paralegal/Legal Assistant - Mid-Level</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G55S6XWGG3X8MSB5X&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G55S6XWGG3X8MSB5X&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Paralegal Our client, a major manufacturer located in the Twin Cities area is looking to add a career paralegal to staff. Qualified candidates will need to have 3-5 years of experience, primarily in litigation ( product liability, antitrust, government filings, personal injury, environmental, intellectual property, bankruptcy, insurance, etc.) The types of cases supported vary and there is on-going collaboration with outside counsel. Project management experience is a plus. Educational requirement is a Bachelors degree and Paralegal certification from an ABA approved program. In addition, candidates will need to be self starters, goal oriented, with strong communication skills and a business orientation. Competitive salary and full benefits available. If you are interested in this position and would like to be considered, please click the Apply Now button to submit your resume. One of our recruiters will follow up with you if you meet the criteria listed above. This position is offered by Kelly Legal Managed Services, a division of Kelly Services, Inc. , a Fortune 500 company headquartered in Troy, MI. About Kelly Services ® Kelly Services, Inc. (NASDAQ: KELYA, KELYB) is a leader in providing workforce solutions. Kelly ® offers a comprehensive array of outsourcing and consulting services as well as world-class staffing on a temporary, temporary-to-hire, and direct-hire basis. Serving clients around the globe, Kelly provided employment to more than 540,000 employees in 2013. Revenue in 2013 was $5.4 billion. Visit kellyservices.com and connect with us on Facebook , LinkedIn and Twitter . Download WorkWire ™ , a free career and employment resource iPad® app by Kelly Services. iPad is a trademark of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries. App Store is a service mark of Apple Inc. Our law specialty places professionals with Fortune 500 corporations and major law firms around the globe. Drawing from its database of thousands of legal professionals, Kelly offers a variety of positions, ranging from litigation attorneys and senior counsel to legal administrators and paralegals. Want more information? Visit kellyservices.com/law Connect with us on</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Patient Educator/Part Time health/Contractor/RN</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHQ6W970VXG2XL35SW1&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHQ6W970VXG2XL35SW1&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Patient Educator/Part Time health/Contractor/RN ZOLL, manufacturer of the world’s first wearable defibrillator, is seeking Patient Service Representatives to train patients in the use of the LifeVest. This is the perfect opportunity for the health professional with patient care and teaching experience to supplement his or her income. A typical LifeVest patient is in the hospital awaiting discharge, and the PSR sets up the equipment and trains the patient and caregivers on the LifeVest. They also follow up with patients as needed to assure patient understanding and satisfaction. PSRs retain the flexibility to accept or decline assignments as their schedules dictate. Most assignments can be scheduled during free time – before/after work, and on days off.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Restaurant Manager</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H75276R5VS0KJ5FCJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H75276R5VS0KJ5FCJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: The manager is responsible for leading department-level restaurant operations; models and demonstrates leadership that is grounded in the Red Lobster Core Values. Successful performance is measured by consistent delivery of balanced results through our systems, methods and procedures from the perspective of all our stakeholders. This leads to sustained growth in sales and profits achieved through personal, people, business and results leadership. Job Requirements * Current , salaried management experience in a high- volume full service restaurant is preferred * Strong passion for culinary excellence and guest service * Proven ability to develop team * Knowledge of systems, methods and processes that contribute to great execution * Stable job history which demonstrates upward career and salary progression</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Property Operations Specialist</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F5DC6PP6TDWTBVZT7&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F5DC6PP6TDWTBVZT7&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job Summary The Property Operations Specialist provides oversight and supervision of day-to-day operations to ensure long-term viability of the property. This position frequently requires independent judgment, timely management of deadlines as well as discretion in carrying out responsibilities. Minimum Job Requirements Related college education and/or a combination of education and minimum 3 years property management experience preferably in healthcare setting. Strong experience in managing Class A Office Properties required Knowledge/Skills/Abilities: Prior experience negotiating, preparing and executing contracts. Computer proficiency with strong knowledge of Excel and MS Word. Ability to easily learn new business specific software programs as needed Prior experience with property management software. Previous marketing and leasing experience. Excellent written and verbal communication and interpersonal skills and ability to work well with a variety of individuals both inside and outside the company. Strong self-management and organization skills. Prior experience in budget preparation and management as well as understanding financial reports. Effective leadership and supervision skills. Strong multi-tasking abilities with the ability to handle competing deadlines, flexible and adaptable (open to change). Ability to effectively handle difficult and sensitive issues and maintain confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Estate Coordinator</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV8476W7BHSRZSVDRD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV8476W7BHSRZSVDRD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Well known Property Management firm area hasimmediate need for Real Estate Coordinator. Only those who want to be the center of expertise should apply! Answer calls and handle tenant needs Responsible for handling e-mail correspondence and creating letters and memos Support the Sr. Property Manager with calendar management and Excel reports Assist with accounts payables and accounts receivables Great opportunity for advancement within the Commercial Property Management field COMPANY PROFILE: InternationalReal Estate services company with regional headquarters in the Houstonarea. Great organization for individualsinterested in the Real Estate, Property Management or Mortgage industry. Publicly traded organization focused on growth Recognition, cultivation and rewards for your talent Opportunities for challenges, learning and advancement with a company aligned with a long term aggressive growth strategy Promotes individual professional growth and development Broader opportunities to advance more because more positions exists Identification with large, well-known company can help establish you as one of the top people in your profession Strong financial resources, strong customer base and strong name brand LOCATION: Openings available in Galleria and Northwest Houston Free Covered parking Beautiful state of the art building Shopping &amp; Restaurants near by Easy access on and off freeways</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Customer Success Specialist I</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL7J761HLK3CJV1N2Z&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL7J761HLK3CJV1N2Z&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job Summary The Customer Success Specialist I will be responsible for acting as a key member of the Customer Success team to provide training and proactive product checks for assigned cost centers. The Success Specialist I will work throughout the client lifecycle to ensure key products are functioning correctly ensuring the highest possible product ROI and adoption. This individual will also handle account assessments and product training sessions on an on-demand basis as part of a team queue. Major Responsibilities/Activities Conduct customer-specific Admin and User training for Standard and Configured customers, appropriate for the intended audience. Conduct regular performance reviews with key stakeholders, including providing product roadmap insights and key recommendations. Assist with account research and ROI presentation generation Target opportunities for expansion and value add Recommend additional customer products/services that align with strategic objectives for each account Subject matter expert and proficient at acquiring ongoing marketplace intelligence by researching trends and best practices, reading business publications, seeking out learning and development opportunities and utilizing internal training resources. Drive retention and renewal of assigned accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Management Trainee</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J7QC6FD4TGB4PXCR2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J7QC6FD4TGB4PXCR2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Regardless of college major or professional experience, nearly 100% of our full-time employees start out in our Management Training Program. This allows everyone to learn our business from the ground up and understand how they play a significant role in seeing it succeed. Once you've completed your initial orientation and training, you'll be assigned to a branch office in your home area and the hands-on training begins. You'll learn valuable business skills from capable mentors who were once in your shoes. Nearly 100% of all our managers and corporate executives started out as Management Trainees. During your first year, you will actively participate in everything from sales and marketing and customer service to operations and finance. As you progress, you will be tested and evaluated to determine your proficiency in these areas. Successful completion of these tests and evaluations will result in rewards, pay increases and the opportunity for continued promotions. As you progress, increasingly more opportunities will become available to you. You can choose, as most people do, to continue your rewarding ascent within our Rental Operations managerial track or you can explore one of many other exciting options including Fleet Management, Human Resources, Car Sales, Accounting, Marketing and more. As a Management Trainee, you are empowered to make business decisions that greatly affect your career as well as the bottom line. You'll gain responsibility for developing new business and maintaining current relationships. You'll be responsible for understanding cost control, reading your branch's P&amp;L statement and understanding what it takes to run a profitable business. You will also learn how to deliver superior customer service. We will teach you how to effectively communicate, influence and interact with all types of customers, vendors and co-workers. You'll learn proper sales techniques to problem solving and conflict management. Those skills will provide you with the opportunity to market to local business partners and build solid, long-lasting relationships with key business decision-makers. In your development to become a successful manager at Enterprise, you'll learn how to mentor, train, develop, manage and promote a staff of your own. Equal Opportunity Employer - Minorities/Women/Veterans/Disabled Must be at least 18 years old Bachelors degree required. A minimum of 6 months work experience in sales, customer service or management/supervisory. Will consider leadership experience in organizations/clubs, volunteer work or community service OR experience as a college or professional athlete in lieu of work experience. Must have a valid driver's license in with no more than two moving violations and/or at fault accidents in the past 3 years. No DWI/DUI/DWAI or other drug and/or alcohol-related convictions on driving record in past 5 years. Must be authorized to work in the United States and not require work authorization sponsorship by our company for this position now or in the future.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Sr. Associate Director, Federal Relations</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT0CX69SZCWQB51Z8W&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT0CX69SZCWQB51Z8W&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Represent the American Hospital Association's (AHA's) interests before the United States Congress. Primary goals are to promote hospitals' interests with primary congressional committees with greatest importance to hospitals. Assume a leadership role in legislative issues affecting hospitals and to develop, advocate and articulate AHA's position which will result in a positive impact on the political environment facing members, to have the support and understanding of the members, and to assist the members in interpreting and thriving in that environment. Requirements EDUCATION 1. Bachelors Degree 2. Requires a degree in political science, government, healthcare, law or a related discipline. EXPERIENCE 1. 5-7 years 2. Significant political, substantive, legislative, and trade association experience, including political experience as staff to a Member of Congress preferably with Committee responsibilities that include health care or appropriations. 3. Requires a background with a trade association involved in health care issues. 4. Requires a background in legislative representation, thorough knowledge of health care issues, outstanding writing and speaking skills. 5. Outstanding writing and speaking skills. 6. Ability to work well with people in a conciliatory manner in a high-pressure environment. 7. Willingness to travel. TECHNICAL Expertise with Microsoft Office Suite (MS Word, PowerPoint, Excel) Benefits We offer an excellent total compensation package, which includes medical/dental coverage (PPO/HMO), vision care, life insurance, short and long-term disability plans, 401(k), tuition reimbursement, paid vacation/holidays/sick days, wellness programs and more! The American Hospital Association (AHA) is an Equal Opportunity Employer: EOE AA M/F/Vet/Disability. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to their race, color, religion, national origin, sex, protected veteran status or disability. We will provide reasonable accommodation for individuals protected by Section 503 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, the Vietnam Era Veterans' Readjustment Assistance Act of 1974 and Title I of the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990. The AHA participates in the E-Verify Program.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Chief Business Officer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT4WG60N0W5NSX35KK&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT4WG60N0W5NSX35KK&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Position Title: Chief Business Officer Department: Office of the President Report To: President and CEO Job Summary: The Chief Business Officer (CBO) would be responsible for all administrative functions such as finance, the budget process, development, HR, IT, membership initiatives, member services, and event activities. The CBO would also contribute to the development of GPhA’s strategic goals and objectives. Apply to Kathy Altman: Specific Duties and Responsibilities: Office management: oversee administrative functions, ensuring smooth daily operations Ensure the continued financial viability of GPhA’s operational work through sound fiscal management Plan, coordinate and execute the annual budget Working with the Senior Director of Finance, manage and oversee all financial and business planning activities Upgrade and implement an appropriate system of policies, internal controls, accounting standards and procedures Ensure that relevant financial data is presented to the President and CEO and senior management team on a timely basis Ensure the ongoing maintenance and updating of information systems and infrastructure Working with the Senior Director of Human Resources, manage and oversee the human resource function for GPhA including recruitment, hiring and compensation; benefits administration and oversight; professional training and development, including new employee orientation; retention strategies; and regulatory oversight and legal compliance Ensuring that the human resource function is properly resourced and represented with the senior management team Working with the Senior Director of Meetings, manage and oversee the management of the multiple events that GPhA hosts annually Working with senior staff, manage and coordinate aggressive membership, member services, and business development initiatives</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Media Marketing Coordinator</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL5926PTDZHCNDCRJZ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHL5926PTDZHCNDCRJZ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job Summary : The Media Coordinator provides support to the Media Buyer/Planner and Media Director/Manager for all client inquiries. This position answers telephone calls, collects information for the Media Department, assists in the preparation of presentation materials, media plans and/or grids, full media proposals and client analysis. Essential Job Functions: Taking all telephone calls from media representatives, gathering information required and referring them to the Media Buyer/Planner &amp; Media Director/Manager when necessary. Participating in meetings with media representatives when requested by Media Buyer and/or Media Director/Manager. Assist in building relationships with a wide variety of media suppliers. Attending industry functions, such as press conferences, client and agency functions or product launches as needed during the business day and/or after hours. Attending other non-media-specific industry functions, promoting a positive company image to industry colleagues, media, suppliers and competitors. Assisting in all media planning functions, as required by the Media Director/Manager and/or Media Buyer/Planner. Providing research for media planning, including but not limited to calling publications and other media, reviewing media kits to obtain information, meeting with media representatives and obtaining industry specific marketing data from trade. Preparing (word processing) media recommendations as required. Assisting in the coordination of direct mail contracts and specific pieces. Maintaining all client media files. · All other duties as assigned.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Mechanical Design Engineer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHN7M778X329QH7CQ71&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHN7M778X329QH7CQ71&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: This is an excellent opportunity for someone looking for a creative hands-on position with a stable and growing company. My client in Huntley, IL is looking for a Mechanical Design Engineer to assist in product development. This Mechanical Design Engineer will design and build Industrial machines and devices from conception to finished product. This is a temp to hire position, but will consider direct hire for the right candidate. The salary for this position will be commensurate with education and experience. If interested please contact Matt and or call 815-788-8556.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Year End Specialist/Business Analyst</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV3C168G5ZFHM12MJD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV3C168G5ZFHM12MJD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Conde Group ( www.condegroup.com ), a consulting and staffing firm based in Southern California, focuses on helping our clients to acquire and retain the best talent to create a competitive advantage. Currently, we are seeking a direct hir e Year End Specialist/Business Analyst in San Francisco, CA . Job Descriptions: The Business Analyst is responsible for the daily processing and oversight of key compliance and regulatory functions within Item Processing. The individual will possess a strong sense of urgency and will be sensitive in meeting strict deadlines applicable to federal and state laws and regulations. The Business Analyst will ensure sound processes are in place in order to improve efficiency, reduce risk, and support new business. The individual will work with various internal business units to ensure overall Bank compliance is met. The individual will have significant discretion in structuring priorities and will use independent judgment to assess issues and determine solutions. The individual will be responsible for enforcing policies, internal processes, operational procedures, compliance, risk, and departmental reporting. The analyst must be able to make sound decisions and communicate effectively with team members, other departments, senior management, and occasionally the client. The individual will have excellent verbal and written communication skills and the ability to work across all groups. The candidate should be well-versed in Excel and Access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Certified Nurse Aide- CNA</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV1896KPR64ZJ4CJMB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV1896KPR64ZJ4CJMB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Senior Care Centers is the largest growing long term care and rehabilitation organization in the state of Texas. We focus on delivery of clinical care, while recognizing our customers’ right to decide and participate in their overall plan of care. We strive to treat our residents with dignity, respect and empathy. Ultimately our goal is to make their stay worthwhile and enjoyable while they are within our care. JOB TITLE: CERTIFIED NURSE ASSISTANT (CNA) REPORTS TO : Charge Nurse RESPONSIBILITIES: Responsible for assisting residents with activities of daily basis to promote resident independence and dignity. ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS: · Follow resident assignment schedule as made out by charge nurse, or Unit Manager. This requires the ability to be mentally alert and communicate verbally and in writing information regarding resident’s condition and care. · Lift, move and transfer residents as required. Check and reposition residents every two- (2) hours or more frequently as instructed. This involves the ability to safely transfer residents who cannot bear their own weight. It also involves the ability to safely perform movements such as pushing, pulling, lifting, bending, kneeling, reaching and lifting in excess of 150 pounds with or without reasonable accommodations. Manual dexterity required performing tasks in assisting residents with their personal needs. · Bathe, shower, shampoo, shave, comb hair, dress appropriately, nail care (routine fingernails and toe nails,) of any residents assigned. · Answer call lights in a timely manner. Be alert to resident’s comforts and needs. Answer their requests promptly. · Assist and/or totally feed residents. · Keep resident clean and dry, toileting or providing incontinent care. Assist with bowel and bladder care. Empty Foley catheter bags, records amount and type. Give perineal care according to policy. Willingness and ability to tolerate washing hands with soap frequently throughout the day. · Observe all residents and report anything unusual or abnormal to Charge Nurse. Ability to safely care for residents in a patient and respectful manner despite resident’s lack of cooperation and/or combativeness. · Provide a supportive, protective, and safe environment for residents. Provide care in a kind, compassionate manner and while able to endure continuous stress of caring for residents and working with their families, including caring for residents who may be disoriented, irrational, highly agitated, susceptible to abrupt mood swings, or susceptible to physically aggressive behavior. · Follow safety guidelines. Promptly remove and clean up urine or bowel excretions and other spills or safety hazards. · Regularly bends stoops and crouches to assist with ambulation and Range of Motion exercises to maintain or improve resident’s level of functioning. · Take vital signs, weight, and collect specimen’s give colostomy care and/or catheter care. · Clean wheelchairs, beds, nursing equipment, resident personal hygiene items, and other items as directed. Requires the ability to lift at least 25 pounds and remove assistive devices to clean properly. · Safely utilize equipment. Report any equipment needing service or repair immediately. · Participate in emergency fire or disaster drills and other in-service training as scheduled. Must be able to safely ascend and descend stairwells and assist in an evacuation. · Assist in care of a resident after death. · Follow Universal Safety Precautions in order to protect one self, residents and other staff members. Rinse soiled linen in preparation to be sent to the laundry this involves the capability to withstand strong foul odors and. Willingness and ability to wear, tolerate and use protective clothing and equipment needed in the carrying out of duties, i.e. latex gloves. · Must be capable of maintaining regular attendance in accordance with facility absence policies. · Complete assigned training on time and/or attend training classes when scheduled. · Take residents to smoking area and assist and monitor residents with smoking. · Use appropriate work place behavior and adhere to dress code at all times. · Uses tactful, appropriate communications in sensitive and emotional situations. · Promotes positive public relations with residents, family members and guests. OTHER DUTIES: · Performs other duties as assigned. · Encourage residents to maintain their highest possible independence, while maintaining their resident’s rights. · Provide pre-and post-meal grooming, including washing hands and face, providing oral hygiene, toileting, and assisting to the dining room. Maintain proper oral hygiene by assisting or brushing teeth, providing denture care and keeping mouth clean. · Participate in department meetings and family meetings as directed. · Participate in teaching and promoting self-care for residents. · Clean water pitchers and keep fresh water at the bedside. Offer water and/or juices several times to residents during each shift. WORK SCHEDULE: As assigned; including some weekends, evenings and holidays. Non-Exempt Position. PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS: Able to lift 100 pounds, if necessary, to assist fallen resident. Able to lift 25 pounds for routine performance of essential functions. AA/EEO/M/F/D/V</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Accountant III</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H71F5ZMB91XQQ2YX4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H71F5ZMB91XQQ2YX4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: International company located in downtown Ft. Worth is looking for a senior accountant to join their team. Candidates must have: • 4 year accounting degree • 3 – 5 years’ experience, public accounting is a plus • CPA or CPA candidate • Strong MS Office skills • Hyperion Essbase • Ability to work OT during month/quarter end Responsibilities will include: • Applying GAAP • SEC filings • Technical account reconciliations • External financial statement preparation Salary will be between $70,000 - $75,000, depending on experience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Research Methods Instructor - Adjunct</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F4C1651D2LYRJ1QLV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F4C1651D2LYRJ1QLV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: ITT Technical Institute is a leading provider of technology-oriented postsecondary degree programs designed to help students develop skills and knowledge they can use to pursue career opportunities in a variety of fields. At our more than 140 accredited ITT Technical Institutes located in approximately 39 states, we predominately provide career-focused degree programs of study in fields involving technology, criminal justice, business, and nursing to approximately 60,000 students. Today, we continue to execute our model, add new programs of study, and grow at a very rapid pace building new campus locations across the country. At ITT Tech we are committed to helping men and women develop the skills and knowledge to pursue many opportunities in fields involving technology, criminal justice, and business. The Research Methods Instructor is responsible for providing quality instruction to students by ensuring student satisfaction through the classroom or laboratory setting according to the program objectives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside Sales Representative</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G0RN75Q3C6VWKP12J&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G0RN75Q3C6VWKP12J&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Inside Sales Representative If you're a driven customer service/inside sales professional who is looking for a growth opportunity within a dynamic environment, an Inside Sales Representative role with Bray Sales Southeast is a great fit! Enjoy working with a strong community of colleagues who support and celebrate each other's professional wins. You will join our stable, growing company that is backed by a diversified organization. Success in this position will lead to increased earnings and the potential transition to an outside sales rep role. Join our team of energetic, hard-working professionals and watch your career take off to new heights. Bray Sales Southeast is a full service distribution center for the Bray Controls Factory. The branch covers both North and South Carolina for all Bray products in all industries. Bray International, Inc. is a leading global manufacturer of industrial valves, actuators, and related control products used by process industries in a wide variety of applications. This diverse market presence provides stability under even the toughest economic circumstances. Bray prides itself on delivering products of the highest quality and value, with an ever-expanding product line that aims to satisfy our customers’ unique needs. Since its founding in 1986, Bray has achieved tremendous success and growth. The company’s truly entrepreneurial vision has driven an expansion to Divisions in over 20 countries and a distribution network that surpasses 300 locations worldwide. Our employees are the company’s greatest asset and as such we are committed to their continual development. We hold high expectations for our employees and we provide the necessary tools and resources that enable them to take on many responsibilities and perform at their highest potential. Furthermore, Bray has a team of passionate high-energy leaders and managers that constantly challenge the company to pursue new opportunities and to surpass its goals. Bray International is an Equal Opportunity Employer and a drug and tobacco free work environment. Employment is contingent upon successful completion of a background check investigation and a drug screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Clinical Instructor - Dental Hygiene - Part-Time</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F2QN6R5PZ7FRKD983&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F2QN6R5PZ7FRKD983&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: As an instructor at Carrington College you will be responsible for delivering a quality educational experience for the students in the courses that you teach through ensuring that curriculum is up-to-date, that effective delivery methods are employed, and that all students are treated in a fair and equitable manner.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales Manager</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F7QQ6VS2LCCM6BFDN&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F7QQ6VS2LCCM6BFDN&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Selling Power Magazine rated SCI/Dignity Memorial #31 in the Top 50 Best Service Companies to Sell For (2013)! We are growing our sales force by 30% this year to meet the increasing demand for our products and services. This opportunity represents exceptional income potential, training, and career advancement! We are looking for a strong, professional Sales Manager for the Northern New Jersey Market. The Sales Manager’s responsibilities will include the following: Ability to motivate individuals with excellent communication skills, incredible relationship-building abilities, and a natural talent to lead Managing Sales Professionals, including motivating Sales Teams to become highly productive in a professional environment The Sales Manager will coach and mentor the Sales Counselors to manage leads and train the team on customer service and satisfaction, prospecting, product knowledge, sales presentations, closing skills, product/service pricing, terms, paperwork, and interpreting sales guidelines Help prepare yearly sales quotas and ensure that quotas are achieved Recruit and hire Sales Counselors Provide Sales Counselors with proper training regarding sales techniques, legal requirements, and company products, policies , and procedures Review and evaluate the Sales Team’s performance Handle personnel issues concerning the Sales Team Conduct and assist in the Weekly Sales Meeting Ensure all contracts and paperwork is completed and returned accurately and in a timely manner Work in the Field with the Sales Team Traveling locally is required</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Yard Associate</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H1TL6DDZX60F0TKQ4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H1TL6DDZX60F0TKQ4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Sunbelt Rentals, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Ashtead Group plc, is one of the largest equipment rental companies in the U.S. Based in Fort Mill, S.C., we serve the needs of a wide variety of customers – from commercial, residential, municipal and specialized service industries to weekend do-it-yourselfers. With a large network of locations nationwide, we deliver the equipment you need and provide a superior level of customer service. At Sunbelt Rentals we aspire to be the best player in the industry, not the biggest. We are seeking a skilled Yard Associate to join our team. We understand the diverse talent of our employees is a driving force behind our success. That’s why we invest in your career with competitive compensation , extensive on-the-job training , and plenty of opportunities to work, from entry level, to senior management positions!</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Associate Dentist  DDS / DMD (General Dental Practice)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J3635VYXVGQBJ4YJS&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J3635VYXVGQBJ4YJS&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Aspen Dental is on a mission to give America a healthy mouth. By joining Aspen Dental you are not only making a statement that you are committed to providing quality care but you are also becoming a part of a collaborative network of dental professionals. For an estimated 47 million Americans, lack of access to affordable dental care is a real problem and by aligning with Aspen Dental you can be part of the solution. As a dentist, you'll have clinical autonomy and be able to focus your entire day on providing quality patient care. You will have the support of highly skilled, trained office staff and the operational aspects of the practice will be taken care of by our business teams. Enjoy access to free continuing education and training and the opportunity to own your own practice through the Practice Ownership Program. As a dentist with Aspen, you can expect to see a steady flow of new patients every day that are ready to get their smile back. Your daily procedures will include restoration (fillings), crown and bridge and core build-ups (veneers, onlays, inlays), extractions, removable prosthodontics, and providing comprehensive treatment plans. And at the end of the day we know that you'll find your career is truly rewarding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Developer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB747S763CJYMZ3R1RY&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JB747S763CJYMZ3R1RY&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Job is located in Windsor, CT. Hi, Please review the below job details and let me know if you are interested, ============================================== Position : Software Developer Location : Windsor CT Duration : Fulltime The responsibilites of the developer position are to: Design, develop, and maintain applications and systems that meet requirements Develop and support custom web interfaces ( ASP.NET , JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, XML, CSS) Create, test, implement, modify, place into production and maintain SSIS packages that automate ETL processes Create, test, implement, modify, place into production and maintain SSRS reports that enhance transparency and control Provide database design, support and troubleshooting (SQL Server 2005 / 2008) Coordinate the resolution of production issues with internal staff, external clients, and vendors (data providers) Perform systems analysis, troubleshooting, and contribute to documentation</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Bridge Inspection Engineer EIT (Roanoke)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F1VY5W01XZN8X4HJD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F1VY5W01XZN8X4HJD&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Open Date: 11/17/14 Close Date 12/01/14 5:00 p.m. An Equal Opportunity Employer - M/F/D/V. AAP. Drug -free workplace. E-verify Applicant must be legally authorized to work in the U.S. We do not typically sponsor H - 1B visas. Must apply online through corporate website at www.clarknexsen.com Job Description We seek to hire a Bridge Inspection Engineer (EIT) to work within the Transportation Division in our Roanoke, VA office. This position will be responsible for assisting in various aspects of a bridge safety inspection projects while working under the close supervision and guidance of a licensed bridge engineer. Typical responsibilities include assisting in field inspections to include bridge safety inspections and structural condition assessments, and preparing bridge safety inspection reports. May be required to perform bridge inspection team leader duties as assigned which include the planning and organization of a bridge safety inspection or a group of bridge safety inspections, the performance and completion of said inspections, the coordination and field liaison of various access equipment and maintenance of traffic providers as well as the owner/agency as appropriate, and the completion of the bridge safety inspection report. General responsibilities include but are not limited to the following: Serving as an Assistant or Inspection Team Leader for NBI bridge safety inspections Writing bridge safety inspection reports or reviewing inspection reports written by other engineers/inspectors Supervising and directing the work of inspectors and CADD technicians as appropriate Perform or assist in the development and calculation of bridge live load ratings Office and field coordination with vendors, sub-consultants, and owners/agencies as appropriate Preparation of marketing and presentation materials as directed Obtain guidance from Senior Bridge Engineers and the Department Head as necessary to resolve technical and coordination issues and conflicting criteria Complying with the company’s quality control practices and procedures Working with, responding to, and taking direction from the Managing Principals, Project Managers, Operations Directors, and senior management Participate in team meetings and coordinating efforts with other team members Mentoring and monitoring the professional development of junior bridge inspection staff Project responsibilities include but are not limited to the following: Perform bridge inspection tasks as directed Serve in the role of Bridge Inspection Team Leader on projects as assigned Preparing or assisting in preparation of scope and fee proposals for bridge inspection projects Preparing accurate and complete bridge inspection reports for project submittals Reviewing calculations and all work products produced by inspectors assigned to the project as appropriate Reviewing all work products produced by support staff assigned to the project Coordinate work product with other disciplines, as appropriate Adhere to project, department, and corporate QA/QC procedures as appropriate Adhere to project budget and schedule Essential Abilities include but are not limited to the following: Travel an average of 50% of the time Work may involve times outside normal working hours and on weekends Work outdoors with varying terrain and all types of weather Stand, walk, and climb for 8+ hours a day Be able to lift 50-60 lbs. and operate bridge inspection equipment Be able to work at heights, over water, and in confined spaces Education Bachelor’s Degree from an ABET-accredited college or university in one of the following disciplines: Civil Engineering (structural emphasis) Civil and Environmental Engineering (structural emphasis) Civil Engineering Technology (structural emphasis) Licenses, Certifications, and Accreditations Successful completion of NHI Course #130055 Safety Inspection of In-Service Bridges is desirable Must have earned the designation of EI or EIT in at least one US state, preferably in the local jurisdiction Ability to complete all requirements for PE licensure within 72 months after being hired Active participation in NSPE, ASCE, or other related professional organizations is desirable Software Skills A Bridge Inspection Engineer (EIT) should be able to effectively utilize current company software programs for word processing, e-mail, accounting, and information management. Working familiarity with analysis, design, and production software including but not limited to Microsoft Excel and Access, AASHTOWareBrR, and Microstation, to a point of being able to understand the capabilities and limitations of the programs and interact with the support staff in their use of the software is highly desirable. Career Experience Minimum of two (2) years of bridge inspection experience is desirable Knowledge and familiarity of the National Bridge Inspection Standards, AASHTO Manual for Bridge Evaluation, and the Bridge Inspector’s Reference Manual Prior experience in the design and/or construction of bridges is desirable Prior experience on VDOT and/or Federal bridge inspection projects is desirable Successful completion of NHI Course #130053 Bridge Inspection Refresher Training, #130078 Fracture Critical Inspection Techniques for Steel Bridges, and/or #130087 Inspection and Maintenance of Ancillary Highway Structures is desirable Other Criteria and Considerations Possess excellent written communication skills, being able to prepare effective and concise documents and correspondence. Possess strong verbal communication skills, being comfortable with and able to make presentations to a variety of groups Have an enthusiastic, client-oriented, can-do attitude with a desire to provide outstanding professional services Be dedicated to his or her professional development as well as the success of colleagues and the firm as a whole Be dedicated to the advancement of the engineering profession</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Lead Java UI Developer</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F7635W7HNBB6J66JW&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F7635W7HNBB6J66JW&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: • Are you seeking an opportunity to show you exceptional skills and knowledge? Are you looking for a company which provides you with dynamic and challenging work environment every single day? If yes, look no further.... We are probing for individuals who are skilled, knowledgeable and are ready to work in a fast paced environment to deliver top notch solutions to cater business needs. About Nabors • Nabors owns and operates the world's largest land-based drilling rig fleet and has one of the largest completion services and workover and well servicing rig fleets in North America. Our company is a leading provider of offshore platform workover and drilling rigs in the U.S and multiple international markets. Nabors provides innovative drilling technology and equipment, directional drilling and comprehensive oilfield services in most of the significant oil and gas markets in the world. • Canrig Drilling Technology Ltd., with revenues of approximately $400M, provides equipment, tools, services, and software products to oil and gas companies worldwide to improve the safety and efficiency of the drilling process. Our workforce, like our technology, is rapidly expanding and looking for a qualified Lead Java Developer. SUMMARY DESCRIPTION: SUMMARY DESCRIPTION: Lead Java Developer, working with the team will design and implement technical solutions to meet the needs of business communities in various divisions. In this role, the Lead Developer will be working with technical leads, business stakeholders and project managers to understand the requirements, formulate technical designs, work with a technical team to implement and test the solutions to ensure compliance to requirements and technical standards. The Lead Developer will also provide development support to production applications. A successful candidate should have a passion for leading technical teams, good design, analytical and programming skills with Java background. The candidate should possess a proven track record of leading technical teams, defining and delivering high quality solutions through the application of software development best practices. Ideal candidate should have at least 2 years of leadership experience and 10 years of over all programming experience, focused around different Java technologies. The candidate should be able to demonstrate their experience through a presentation and a technical discussion of his work. PRIMARY DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES: • Lead technical teams • Design and develop Java applications under tight deadlines • Be capable of making clear technology decisions • Participate in technical and architectural reviews throughout the course of development • Coordinate, coach and mentor other team members • Help management with personnel evaluations • Other duties as assigned in an agile team environment</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>NGS Developer Advisor Sensitive - 96990</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G2696WY1VLYSL2WC4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G2696WY1VLYSL2WC4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: WellPoint is the nation's leading health benefits company serving the needs of approximately 28 million medical members nationwide. National Government Services (NGS) is one of the largest Medicare contractors in the country, serving nearly 200,000 providers and suppliers and over 20 million customers with Medicare in 20 states and five U.S. territories. Bring your expertise to our innovative, achievement-driven culture, and you will discover lasting rewards and the opportunity to take your career further than you can imagine. Our Developer Advisor is responsible for programming on specific application subsets of the company's application portfolio, participating in all phases of the development and maintenance life cycle, typically for an assigned business unit or corporate department and utilizing various customer technology platforms. Primary duties may include, but are not limited to: Maintains active relationships with customers to determine business requirements and leads requirements gathering meetings. Owns the change request process and may coordinate with other teams as necessary. Develops and owns list of final enhancements. Develops and defines application scope and objectives and prepares technical and/or functional specifications from with programs will be written. Performs technical design reviews and code reviews. Ensures unit test is completed and meets the test plan requirements, system testing is completed and system is implemented according to plan. Assesses current status and supports data information planning. Coordinates on-call support and ensures effective monitoring of system. Maintains technical development environment. Mentors others and may lead multiple or small to medium sized projects. Facilitates group sessions to elicit complex information on requirements clarification, design sessions, code reviews and troubleshooting issues. Supports vendor evaluation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Trainee Recruitment Consultant -Fast Career progression- Great$</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H81M5YXNC9CH918YB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3H81M5YXNC9CH918YB&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Trainee / Graduate Recruitment Consultant - New York City, basic + uncapped bonus - realistic first year total on target earnings $80k+! I am currently looking for talented, hardworking individuals with a passion to succeed to join a rapidly growing niche IT recruitment firm based in New York City. This is an amazing opportunity for anyone looking to determine their own income by how hard they work and how good they are at their job. This is not your average 9-5 job, and it is definitely not for the faint-hearted, but if you believe you have what it takes please read on. Previous recruitment experience would be advantageous but not a pre-requisite as we are interested in hearing from; •Hard working &amp; highly driven Graduate caliber candidates •You should be of a positive, confident &amp; enthusiastic nature with excellent communication skills •You must be hard working, prepared to work long hours and you must be comfortable cold calling both candidates and business clients over the phone. Most importantly however, all graduates must have a genuine passion to work in a fast paced, target driven sales environment. In this role you will be responsible for the development and growth of both client and candidate relationships in the market you are assigned to and in order to succeed you will be given industry leading / award winning training in all aspects of sales, recruitment &amp; head-hunting in a first class career development plan. Our senior management team has over 75 years combined recruitment experience so you can literally learn and work with the best recruiters in the industry. We regularly feature in the NY Best Places to work list and are a very employee centric business. This role offers the chance for the right candidate to almost run a mini business and have full control over a market, developing it as you wish. The role is largely phone based but you will have the opportunity to meet with clients in some of the most cutting edge firms in the USA and attend regular product networking events all over the US and Europe, so variety is assured. This is a unique opportunity for the right person to forge a long term lucrative career where you will flourish both professionally and financially as should you join Nigel Frank International, you will be rewarded with a highly competitive remuneration package with a well-structured &amp; incentivized uncapped bonus scheme. With offices in London, New York, San Francisco, Melbourne and Singapore there is a chance to grow on business level with us all over the world. We are open to relocating members of staff throughout the world so you could be living in San Francisco or London this time next year. Other great target-based individual &amp; team incentives at Nigel Frank include; •* Weekend's away (most recently Miami, Amsterdam, Madrid, &amp; Barcelona) all expenses paid •* Exclusive event hospitality (most recently the British and Singapore Grand Prix &amp; Wimbledon Tennis) •* Fine dining at up-scale restaurants on monthly "lunch clubs" •* City night's out including 1st Class train travel, dinner in a Michelin rated restaurant &amp; 5* Hotel Accommodation + VIP club access •* High achiever awards •* Company nights out &amp; more We grow our consultants organically &amp; encourage promotion to management level from within the business making this a unique chance for the right person to start at the bottom as a trainee and work their way up the firm with a genuine career path. To apply: email James Tullett at or I can be reached at 646-863-7575 Recruitment / Recruiter / Trainee / Graduate / Consultant / Headhunting / Head-hunter / Sales / Business Development / New York / NY / NYC / Manhattan / Financial District / Wall Street / Growth / Queens / Brooklyn / New Jersey / Hoboken</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Scheduler (radiology / medical scheduling)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM1ZJ65RW348HPSRC0&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM1ZJ65RW348HPSRC0&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Growth and learning opportunity available for a caring professional that wants to further develop their skills and knowledge in healthcare, while making a difference in patient's lives. We invite you to join our Temecula Valley scheduling department as a Patient Scheduler. This per-diem career opportunity has a Monday - Friday 8:00 am to 5:00 pm schedule, and is located at our high volume outpatient practice in Murrieta, CA. In this medical office position you'll get to: • Answer phones and guide patients through this sometimes difficult process by kindly talking them through the steps and answering their questions and concerns. • Schedule patients for exams, and input/update patient information in our medical system. • Perform insurance verifications and authorizations. • Participate in various projects and/or meetings, and complete other tasks as assigned by management. We offer competitive pay, career advancement opportunities, inter-company transfer opportunities, and a host of other perks! Become a valued member of our growing company by emailing your resume to: Angela.S RadNet is an equal opportunity employer, committed to cultural diversity. RadNet will provide equal consideration for employment to all qualified applicants without regard to their race, religion, ancestry, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, age, disability, marital status, domestic partner status, or medical condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>HVAC/R Technician</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV63S70LVXV9XYNK8M&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV63S70LVXV9XYNK8M&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Progressive Regional Service Company is looking for Experienced and Qualified Technicians in 3 Commercial Areas : HVAC Refrigeration Cooking Equipment Installation and Repair Requires Knowledge in these 4 Elements : Gas Steam Electric Refrigeration Expect to be : Trouble Shooting Interacting Professionally with Customers Working Flexible Hours Lifting up to 75 lbs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Pharmaceutical Inside Sales Account Specialist - Cambridge, MA</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G51J6HFXBYX210Y9T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G51J6HFXBYX210Y9T&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Inside Sales Account Specialist Can you actively engage healthcare professionals about clients’ products as an Inside sales account specialist? Publicis Touchpoint Solutions provides a comprehensive array of multichannel message delivery solutions to the life sciences industry. From in field to inside and from promotional to clinical, Publicis Touchpoint Solutions centers-of-excellence include field sales and service, live video detailing, inside heathcare-credentialed representatives, inside sales and service, clinical health educators, and medical science liaisons. A wide range of vital support solutions—each of which serves all of the company’s message delivery channels—includes recruiting, training, performance management, operations, data/analytics, and compliance. Publicis Touchpoint Solutions provides the human touch to precision multichannel messaging delivered at the right time and through the right channels to achieve maximum impact. Publicis Touchpoint Solutions is a member of the Publicis Healthcare Communications Group. We have partnered with one of the world’s leading biotechnology companies, Genzyme which is dedicated to making a major positive impact on the lives of people with serious diseases. This is an excellent opportunity to be part of a fast paced entrepreneurial company that is expanding its inside sales team in specialty markets to maximize patient care for osteoarthritis. We seek several passionate and experienced Inside Sales Account Specialists to shape the commercial effectiveness of a key brand in the specialist space. This opportunity is for individuals looking to make immediate impact. The successful Inside Sales Account Specialist will effectively engage healthcare professionals in informational/promotional communications about our client’s products through outbound and inbound telephone discussions. The position reports to the Inside Sales Manager and has no direct reports. Work location for this position is in Cambridge/Boston, MA area. Candidates must able to travel up to 10% for sales meetings and quarterly field visits, and must be flexible to work evening hours, depending on the geographical area of assigned accounts. Experience Requirements: • BA/BS degree • 1-2 years B2B/Sales/Healthcare experience • Strong focus on providing customers with superior product and service • Skills/Qualifications • Excellent verbal, written and interpersonal communication skills • Clear, articulate and grammatically sound speech and professional phone manne • Excellent selling/persuasion/presentation skills • Strong rapport building skills • Excellent active listening skills • Good organizational and planning skills • Strong product knowledge and marketing skills • Must be self motivated and disciplined • Strong attention to detail and accuracy in recording/handling client and project information • Excellent judgment/decision making skills • Ability to accurately assess individual situations and draw on prior knowledge, experience and problem solving skills in order to come up with successful solutions • Ability to work independently and as a team member • Flexibility and ability to handle multiple tasks simultaneously • Ability to display high-levels of initiative, effort and commitment successfully complete projects and assignments. • Ability to understand the client’s selling model utilizing product training in order to service and support client’s customers in a variety of scenarios. • Excellent computer skills using Microsoft Office applications • Must be able to deal with people at all levels inside and outside of the company Touchpoint Solutions offers competitive compensation, an incentive plan, 401-K benefits, comprehensive benefits package and the opportunity to grow with the nation’s leader in healthcare sales. If you have a proven record of sales success and the desire to make a positive impact in the healthcare field, we want to hear from you. For immediate consideration, please apply online at www.touchpointsolutions.com . PTS is an equal opportunity employer M/F/V/D. We appreciate your interest in our company, however; only qualified candidates will be contacted. Keywords: Inside Sales, Account Manager, Virtual Representative, Pharmaceutical Sales, Contact Center, Call Floor, Customer Service, Sales *LI-Priority</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Medicare Biller - Hospital Central Business Office</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J2HT6JY194JMMS64H&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3J2HT6JY194JMMS64H&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Description As a Medicare Biller, you will provide billing expertise with the goal of accuracy with every encounter. A successful Medicare Biller works to facilitate resolution of billing issues through attention to detail, problem solving initiative and a dedication to efficiency. Key Responsibilities Under general direction, performs Medicare billing functions Identifies billing errors that prevent claims from being processed in the Electronic Billing System Ensures compliance with applicable laws and regulations Provides feedback on issues impacting Billing production Meets productivity and quality standards as established by management Completes assigned training and education Performs other duties as assigned</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>LVN Case Manager</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV3QT63RDLFZVVG7H9&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV3QT63RDLFZVVG7H9&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: LargeManaged Care Healthcare Organization seeking experienced LVN Case Managers ImmediateInterviews! Location:San Antonio, TX Compensation:$20-$24 per hour (negotiated based on experience) LongTerm temp/ contract opportunity Shift:Monday-Friday 8:30a-5:00p Immediateopenings! •2 positions working telephonically inside of the company's office located in SanAntonio, TX PositionResponsibilities: •Worked with the Geriatric and Medicaid population •Conducting health risk assessments, care coordination and patient education •Review of admissions and discharges to ensure medical necessity and appropriatelevel of care. •Develop, assess and adjust as necessary the care plan and promote desiredoutcome. •Coordinate services between Primary Care Physician (PCP) specialist, CommunityResources, and other medical and non-medical providers as necessary to meet thecomplete medical socio economic needs of clients. •Data enters assessments and authorizations into the system. Forimmediate consideration for the LVN Case Manager role, please email your resume to me and call Tracy Shaw,Recruiting Manager, Phone 1-888-219-6285 ext. 104, Fax 407-478-5596 About Healthcare Support Staffing: WhyYou Should Work With Us: HealthCare Support Staffing, Inc. (HSS), is a proven industry-leading nationalhealthcare recruiting and staffing firm. HSS has a proven history of placingtalented healthcare professionals in clinical and non-clinical positions withsome of the largest and most prestigious healthcare facilities including:Fortune 100 Health Plans, Mail Order Pharmacies, Medical Billing Centers,Hospitals, Laboratories, Surgery Centers, Private Practices, and many otherhealthcare facilities throughout the United States. HealthCare Support Staffingmaintains strong relationships with top providers in healthcare and can assurehealthcare professionals they will receive fast access to great careeropportunities that best fit their expertise. Connect with one of ourProfessional Recruiting Consultants today to see how a conversation can turninto a long-lasting and rewarding career!</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Registered Nurse - Case Manager - CONTRACT TO HIRE</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV51471BD0TP4ZFKWR&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV51471BD0TP4ZFKWR&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Very large and well known managed care/insurance company seeks Registered Nurse - Case Manager for their Franklin, TN facility. This is a contract to hire position. Position Description of Registered Nurse - Case Manager: Registered Nurse - Case Manager assess, plan, implement, coordinate, monitor, and evaluate case management activities across the continuum of care, within the scope of the case manager's license, including: Coordination and service delivery, Physical and psychological factors, Benefit systems and cost benefit, Case management concepts and Community resources. Understand and maintain confidentiality of legal and ethical issues at all times. Check eligibility as per procedure/ client specifications; if there is an eligibility problem, the case manager notifies the caller and consults the case management supervisor. Assess initial clinical information and develop a treatment plan and goals that meet the individual patient's/ client's present needs. Communicate goals and objectives to all pertinent parties. Registered Nurse - Case Manager evaluates and certify all cases for potential complications, and cases that would benefit from alternative care. Assess clinical information at established intervals to evaluate the effectiveness of the case management plan for each patient. Evaluate and communicate the case objectives and goals to the individual patient's case management team. Consult physician advisers to determine the medical necessity and appropriateness of treatment plan goals and objectives. Evaluate all referral sources and their qualifications to assure quality outcomes. Determine the cost effectiveness and medical necessity of alternate treatment. Negotiate with providers when necessary to reduce patient cost. Work closely with the family members of patients to involve them in patient care. Assess the psychological characteristics of wellness and illness.. Maintain an open line of communication with all parties of the individual case management treatment team to include patient, family, payer, and service providers across the continuum of care. key words - Registered Nurse - RN - Case Manager - Certified - Bachelor's - Benefits - Managed Care - Insurance - Health and Wellness .</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Part Time Order Puller</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS3T06NG5K04Z4CTB4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS3T06NG5K04Z4CTB4&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: About Us: Keefe Group, through its affiliates, Keefe Supply, Keefe Commissary Network, Crawford Supply, Access Catalog, Access Securepak®, Access Corrections™ and ICSolutions, is the nation's leading supplier of food products, personal care products, electronics, clothing, technology and telecommunications to the correctional market. Role Overview: We are seeking an Order Puller that will help our team process our orders and provide top delivery services to our clients. This position requires a great level of attention to detail and a team oriented personality to help our team achieve our delivery goals. Job Responsibilities: • Perform daily order set ups, including shipment boxes, skids and carts. • Maintain daily record of orders and processing time. • Pull an average of 22 orders per day or as business requires. • Communicate with the stock team whenever inventory is low. • Process and fill replacement orders according to specific needs. • Complete appropriate paperwork and order kits to complete order deliveries. • Maintain a clean work environment and surrounding work areas.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Collector</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP3WR6WLFLPNDWM3PV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP3WR6WLFLPNDWM3PV&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Under general supervision, but following established policies and procedures coordinates the Collection activities of the Credit Union. Ensures Collection activities are in compliance with state and federal regulations and Credit Union policies and procedures. Maintains the delinquency rate according to Credit Union goals and maximizes the charge-off and recovery process. Performs all duties of a Collector. Responds to questions and/or provides information upon request from members (internal and external). Processes requests/transactions, as appropriate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Resident Assistant</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G26S6ZZFMFTF0Y8MT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3G26S6ZZFMFTF0Y8MT&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Full Time Emeritus at Carmel Valley - 13101 Hartfield Ave, San Diego, CA 92130 A career with Brookdale has never been more rewarding! Brookdale is the only national full-spectrum senior living solutions company and committed to providing the best options for our over 110,000 residents we serve. The services that we offer ensure residents continue to live the lives that they want while also meeting all of their needs along the way. Every day our associates collaborate to guarantee this promise is fulfilled in more than 1,150 communities in 47 states. Our Senior Living Solutions include: Independent Living, Assisted Living, Memory Care, Skilled Nursing, Continuing Care Retirement, Therapy, Hospice, Home Health, and Personalized Living. More than a company, it is a calling. To learn more about Brookdale and how our associates make a difference: Fulfilling Dreams * Record-Breaking Fundraising for Alzheimer’s * Best of the Best Awards * Brookdale Senior Living Solutions * YouTube K ey Responsibilities include: * Assisting residents with activities of daily living to include: bathing, dressing, grooming, toileting, positioning, mobility and incontinence care * Keeping proper care records * Reporting changes in resident's conditions * Providing dining services support * Interacting with internal and external customers in a professional manner while ensuring resident safety and satisfaction is a priority</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>PHA Facilitator</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP2NQ66H8ZDNZ92LLJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHP2NQ66H8ZDNZ92LLJ&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: PHA Facilitator Primary role of the PHA Facilitator is to lead PHAs (HAZOP, LOPA, What-if, HAZID) studies for clients which includes petroleum refining, chemical manufactures, oil and gas upstream and midstream operations, pharmaceutical manufacturing and other industries.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Sales/Agency Owner</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT1H06NVKFFG8M54B3&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHT1H06NVKFFG8M54B3&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Insurance Sales Manager – Customer Service - Insurance Agent About us : Since 1928, Farmer Group, Inc. has been helping people get into business for themselves, but not by themselves! As the third-largest home and auto carrier as well as the top specialty product carrier in the United States, we’re committed to excellence and take pride in providing “The Best Small Business Opportunity in America!" Summary of Insurance Sales Manager – Customer Service - Insurance Agent : Farmers Group is seeking competent and committed Insurance Sales Managers to open their own locations and tenaciously pursue accounts to expand their reach and grow their business. While this may be a large undertaking, as an Insurance Sales Manager, you will not do it alone. We have been recognized as having the “#1 Corporate Training Program" in the country by Corporate Exchange USA &amp; Training Magazine . As you begin to develop your business, you will have access to resources as well as knowledgeable and dedicated support teams that will develop your sales, marketing and customer service skills – ensure your future success in this recession-proof industry. As an Insurance Sales Manager, you will have the training and support of a business partner with over 80 years of experience! Farmers Group is also on an aggressive expansion track: currently planning to double in size by 2020! In this role, you will have uncapped earnings potential and access to the top-rated corporate training available in the U.S. We also offer excellent group benefits packages, incentives and rewards for you and your family! Repsonsibilities of Insurance Sales Manager – Customer Service - Insurance Agent : As an Insurance Sales Manager, you will solicit new prospects, sell our products and services and assist existing clients, as necessary. You will also network within your community – attending networking events, sales conferences and trade shows to market your business and target your preferred audience. Additional responsibilities for the Insurance Sales Manager include : Providing excellent customer service to policyholders Educating customers on their plan options Creating your own daily schedule Obtaining pertinent licenses and keeping them current Staying abreast of evolving industry and product changes Making staff hiring and firing decisions</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Registered Nurse (RN) / Licensed Practical Nurse (LPN)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV2YJ62BGPRCCLYKDW&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV2YJ62BGPRCCLYKDW&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Are you passionate about putting the ‘care’ in Healthcare, then we’re looking for you to join our dedicated nursing team providing outstanding healthcare to patients at our skilled nursing facility. Wickliffe Country Place is currently seeking highly motivated and dependable RN's and LPN's that possess the ability to successfully perform in a fast-paced environment. Wickliffe Country Place is a 170 bed skilled nursing facility that is dedicated to providing the highest quality of care and service to those entrusted to our care. We seek to provide our residents with the care and services necessary to meet all of their clinical and non-clinical needs by hiring the best people we can find. At Legacy Health, we are committed to delivering high quality healthcare marked by our values of integrity, passion, humor and relationships. Our skilled nursing team is an integral part in ensuring that we meet these goals for our residents. We offer a comprehensive benefits package, including: Competitive compensation Healthcare Insurance: Medical, Dental and Life Insurance Short Term Disability 401(k) with Employer Match Vacation and Holiday Pay Leave Time (Sick/Personal) As a Registered Nurse you will be responsible for administering nursing care to ill, injured, convalescent, or disabled patients; involving and communicating with residents and family in care planning decisions. Additional responsibilities include: Monitoring, recording, and reporting symptoms or changes in patients' healthcare conditions Maintaining accurate, detailed reports and electronic healthcare records Recording patients' medical information and vital signs Ordering, interpreting, and evaluating diagnostic tests to identify and assess patient's condition Managing and supervising a skilled nursing team of RN’s or LPN’s</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Server</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR10R643PN2FZVP1B2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHR10R643PN2FZVP1B2&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Servers As a key part to our front-of-the-house team, you will act as our service ambassador, ensuring every guest expectation is met and every experience is a positive one. Your knowledge of the menu and superior people skills will put you at ease, as you interact with guests, and promote merchandise and menu items. Some cleaning and light lifting will be required.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreign Language (Arabic) Speaking Role Player (PT)</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F6ZM62YP8QPGMJVNF&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=J3F6ZM62YP8QPGMJVNF&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: The Arabic Speaking Foreign Language Role Player provides acting services for U.S. Army training efforts during regularly scheduled training exercises.. This is a part-time (PT) position that supports the U.S. Military through roleplaying, cultural awareness training and language translation services. ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES Essential duties and responsibilities include the following. Other duties may be assigned. Responsible for the integration of CNI Core Competencies into daily functions, including: commitment to integrity, knowledge/quality of work, supporting financial goals of the company, initiative/motivation, cooperation/relationships, problem analysis/discretion, accomplishing goals through organization, positive oral/written communication skills, leadership abilities, commitment to Affirmative Action, reliability/dependability, flexibility and ownership/accountability of actions taken. Translates the oral communication of the Arabic language to the oral communication of the English language, and vice-versa. Realistically, accurately and convincingly portrays the native or fluent (Arabic) language, culture and roles in a variety of scenarios. This includes diversified settings and environments, which includes practical, situational and field training exercises. Memorizes critical data contained in each role and scenario, and portrays assigned role with little reliance on or referral to the role script; and ensures familiarity with each role. Provides foreign language speaking while acting out scenario based roles, and does not adlib or provide information to students that is not outlined in the developed role. Conveys information and data in response to student's correct and proper interview skills, questioning and/or elicitation techniques. Responsible for aiding in own self-development by being available and receptive to all training made available by the company. Plans daily activities within the guidelines of company policy, job description and supervisor’s instruction in such a way as to maximize personal output. Responsible for keeping own immediate work area in a neat and orderly condition to ensure safety of self and co-workers. Will report any unsafe conditions and/or practices to the appropriate supervisor and human resources. Will immediately correct any unsafe conditions to the best of own ability. EDUCATION/EXPERIENCE To be considered, you must be able to speak and write Basic English and have strong fluency in Arabic (at least 12th grade level). The ability to understand, read, and speak Urdu at the 12th grade level is preferred as well. Fluency in in other middle-eastern languages and / or dialects is valued. CERTIFICATES, LICENSES, REGISTRATION Must be a U.S. born citizen or U.S. naturalized citizen. Must have the ability to obtain a Secret Security Clearance. LANGUAGE SKILLS Ability to read and interpret documents such as safety rules, operating and maintenance instructions, and procedure manuals in English as well as Arabic. Ability to write routine reports and correspondence. Ability to speak effectively before groups of customers or employees of organization. PI87394541</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Registered Nurses &amp; Certified Nursing Assistants</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM44466GSGXDT8FJBP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHM44466GSGXDT8FJBP&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Registered Nurses &amp; Certified Nursing Assistants Job Description: Guiding Light Hospice is a small family owned and operated business. We have full-time positions available for compassionate, experienced RN’s and CNA’s with hospice or geriatric experience. Bi-lingual preferred. Due to the nature of our business we see patients in their homes, and nursing facilities. All team members meet for IDT meetings in the Yorkville area bi-monthly. Flexibility and the ability to drive in challenging weather, is a must. Professional appearance and able to work with minimal supervision. Our priority is quality of life, customer service and going above and beyond. On-call for continuous care, including every other weekend. There are many benefits to joining our team, but due to our size, health benefits is NOT one of them. Excellent salary offered. Must have car, insurance, and Illinois certification/license in good standing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>MAINTENANCE  TECHNICIAN -  ALABAMA</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV1X66GZ2JHWZJB5WR&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHV1X66GZ2JHWZJB5WR&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: Buger Gulf, LLC a franchisee of Burger King owns and operates 83 Burger King restaurants operating in Alabama, Florida and Georgia with over 2000 employees presently on the payroll. Burger Gulf is owned and operated by Andy Patel, who is well versed in the restaurant industry from managing his other holdings of Applebee's and Ihop Restaurants. Burger Gulf, LLC offers competitive salaries for experienced personnel along with a Great Benefit package to include: Job Summary: Maintenance Techs are responsible for preventive as well as reactive maintenance in the Burger King Restaurants. A technician is assigned to an area to insure the upkeep and success of the restaurants in the designated area. It is the technician's responsibility to troubleshoot, diagnose and correct failed or failing equipment that may interfere with delivering the best customer service possible. Reports to a Director of Maintenance that will direct and guide on day to day activities in the markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Staff Writers/Editor</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS0D15WNVZTMVP90XH&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS0D15WNVZTMVP90XH&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: The Mathematical Association of America, conveniently located in historic Dupont Circle, is seeking a full-time staff writer/editor for their publications department. The mission of the MAA is to advance the mathematical sciences. The MAA is the largest professional association focused on mathematics accessible at the undergraduate level. Membership includes college and university faculty and students; high school teachers; individuals from business, industry, and government; and others who appreciate mathematics. The MAA publishes more than a dozen high-quality textbooks and other mathematics titles annually. It produces three of the most widely read mathematics journals in the world ( The American Mathematical Monthly, Mathematics Magazine, and The College Mathematics Journal ), along with the highly regarded student magazine Math Horizons, the online journal Convergence, the online resource MAA Reviews, and the association newsmagazine MAA FOCUS. The staff writer/editor reports directly to the director of publication and works closely with other MAA staff members and outside resources. Additional information about the MAA and its publications programs can be found on MAA’s website: http://www.maa.org . Excellentbenefits including MAA contribution toward retirement, group health and dental,generous holiday, vacation and sick plan, FSA and more. Salary commensurate with skills andexperience. For consideration, please send all of the following documents: resume, cover letter and salary history to . Principals only; no recruiters or other 3rd parties. This organization does not provide the opportunity for sponsorship nor does it offer relocation expenses. EOE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item><item><title>Part Time Customer Sales Rep</title><link>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS6DF6BWZVPNH79N1R&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</link><guid>http://www.careerbuilder.com/jobseeker/jobs/jobdetails.aspx?siteid=RSS_PD&amp;Job_DID=JHS6DF6BWZVPNH79N1R&amp;ipath=rss_geoip</guid><description>Details: What are we looking for: Have some experience in retail selling environment; retail sales a plusBe able to communicate and interact enthusiastically with customers and team members alikeHave the ability to work well under pressure and maintain accuracyHave the ability to be cross trained and thrive in a multitasking environmentBe able to interact comfortably, enthusiastically and professionally while advising customers on specific equipment, products and merchandise. Be Knowledgeable and fluent on explaining finance charges and Intrest rates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 Z</pubDate></item></channel></rss>